请问……
Do you remember the first time your husband saw you naked?
还记得你和丈夫第一次滚床单时的情景吗
Do you remember what it felt like?
你感觉如何
Do you remember what he felt like?
他又如何
Holy motherfuckin' fuck! Oh, my God!
-卧槽太爽了 -天呐
Holy fuck! Oh, my God!
-见鬼 -我要去了
Wow!
Again? Fuck, yeah.
-再来一次 -太好了
Now, this might be a little harder.
第二题就有点难度咯
Do you remember the second time your husband saw you naked?
你还记得第二次和他滚床单吗
Annie, you coming?
Annie 快点
We're gonna be late. Wake up, sleepyhead!
我们要迟到了 懒鬼 快起床
Annie! Shit.
-Annie -我去
Hey, guys. I, uh, totally overslept.
我不小心睡过头了
- Um, okay. Well, you can meet us. - Okay. That sounds...
- 好吧 那你等会儿来找我们- 我觉得..
I saw your butt. Just standin' there.
我看到你光着屁股站在那里
Did you?
是吗
I never seen your butt before.
我以前没见过它们
I had no choice.
所以我情不自禁
We accidentally left the door open.
我们不小心忘记关上了门
I mean, can you even imagine a world
我是说 你能不能体会到
where you accidentally leave the door open?
忘记关门这个词的严重性
I love fucking you.
我爱艹你
I fucking love you.
艹，我爱你
For Jay and I,
对我和Jay而言
the next few months were a blur
接下来的几个月就是一场
of constant naked, sweaty, ugly, amazing sex.
旷日持久 裸露 咸湿 疯狂的做爱
Okay. I got it.
要来了
On, God!
天呐
I'll probably be pretty hungry after this.
这次完事后我要吃饭
It's been a while since I've eaten.
我已经记不得上次吃东西是什么时候了
I can make you a sandwich.
我给你做个三明治吧
We could probably make a burrito out of shit we have here.
做墨西哥卷也行 但记得不要把这里的任何东西包进去
Okay-
好吧
Oh, no!
噢 不
Holy Mary, mother of...
Mary 尼玛..
And let's face it.
让我们正视它
The erections.
勃起
Oh, God. Do you remember the erections?
天呐你记得吗
Erections everywhere.
他能在任何地方勃起
If the Wind blew.
即使只是微风拂过
If he ate certain foods.
或是吃了什么特定的东西
If he watched any movie.
看了电影
If he got sleepy.
即将入睡
If he woke up.
清晨起床
Good morning.
早上好
Sometimes, I swear his erection
有些时候我是饥渴的
knew I was in the area before Jay did.
比Jay更早进入状态
Annie?
Annie
Everywhere we went, everything we did,
我们所到之处 所做之事
was another opportunity to have sex.
只是为了多一次的亲密接触
Do you think we should be doing this right here?
你觉得我们这样合适吗
Baby, honestly, I don't think anyone
宝贝 说实话
can tell what's happening.
我觉得没人能看出我们在干嘛
It's not that it was just sex.
我们单纯享受滚床单的过程
But we knew that there was always
但我们知道
more sex just around the corner.
还会有无数个下一次
Then, it happened.
而后就到了摊牌的时刻
Dad.
爸
Mom.
妈
Jay and I have some big news.
Jay和我有重要的事要说
We're in love. We're pregnant and we're getting married.
我们相爱了 有孩子了 想要结婚
Come again? Honey, wait. What?
-又结？ -甜心 等等 什么
Are you sure?
你确定吗
Yeah. I took the test three times.
嗯 我用验孕棒测了三次
No, honey. No, I mean,
不不不 我是说
are you sure that now is the right time?
你确定就是现在
You're both very, very young
你们都还非常 非常年轻
and who knows what the future holds?
谁知道未来会发生什么
Uh, Greg?
呃 Greg
Oh. Jay.
噢 Jay
Yeah. Where are you from again?
你能不能再说一次你是从哪儿来的
Mr. and Mrs. Grovner, uh,
Grovner夫妇
I know that we just met.
我知道我和Annie相处的时间很短
But when I first met Annie,
但我对她
I knew that she was the one.
一见钟情
And so I think, once you get to know me,
然后我想 当你们深入了解我之后
you're gonna feel
对我的印象
a lot better about this moment than you do right now
一定会大大改观
because I really love your daughter.
因为我真的很爱你们的女儿
I love you.
我爱你
Oh, boy.
孩子你太让我感动了
Well, goodbye, sex.
好吧 但不要再滚床单了
Dad! Walt.
-爸爸 -Walt.
What? What?
-干嘛 -什么
They're not right, are they?
他们说错了是吗
No, of course not.
大错特错
I don't think.
我不这么想
We're not too young?
我们不年轻吗
Oh, we're young. You know?
不 我们确实还小 但你知道吗
But we definitely know each other.
我们已经深入了解了
Greg, right?
对吗 Greg
Yes, I'm Greg.
对 我是Greg.
Look, here's what I think.
我是这么想的
They're right.
我们确实不知道怎么面对未来
We don't know what the future holds.
他们是对的
But I also think that whatever the world throws at us,
但无论未来有怎样的挑战
let's deal with it, right?
我们会携手应对
Yeah. You know?
但是
But what about the sex part?
滚床单的事要怎么办呢
Are you still gonna wanna have sex with me
当我变成一个怀孕的肥婆
even when I am big and fat and pregnant,
一个母亲
and then later when I'm somebody's mother?
你还会愿意和我滚床单吗
Yeah!
当然
Yeah. Really?
真的吗
Babe, my dick can see the future.
宝贝 我的小伙伴能预知未来
That's why we call it Nostracockus.
所以我们叫它神棍
What about you? Are you gonna wanna have sex with me?
那你呢 你还会想和我滚床单吗
Yes, I'm gonna wanna have sex with you.
无时无刻都在想啊
Yeah? Yes!
-真的 -对
Do you know why I'm gonna wanna have sex with you?
知道我为什么想和你滚床单吗
My butt? Because of your butt, babe.
-难不成是因为我的屁股 -绝对是你的小翘臀 宝贝
We promised ourselves nothing would change.
我们许诺会爱对方如初
That we wouldn't let it.
不让一切改变
And even though it was awkward sometimes,
即使有时很困难
we made it work.
我们总能应对
If you could just turn a little bit more
能不能再转过去点儿
Yep. To the right.
-好 -往右
I think we're good.
位置对了
That's... I'm maxed out. My stomach's in the way.
我的胃要被挤出来了
You know what? I'm gonna grab boob.
那个 我要抓你的奶了
Yeah, just be careful. They're really sensitive.
小心点 他们很敏感
And not in a good way.
方向也不对
Got it. Very gently grabbin' boob.
抓到了 让我轻轻地揉
Okay, gently.
嗯 轻轻地
And here comes the penis.
小弟弟也按耐不住了
That's gonna be the name of my album.
我要用它做相册名
We were determined. And often, successful.
我们下定决心并且成功了
Then came the event.
然后它出生了
Motherfucker!
草
You're doing an amazing job, babe. You're doing great!
宝贝就是这样 你做的很好
Tell her she's doing great!
告诉她她很棒
He's crowning, if you'd like to see.
要不要来看看 孩子的头出来了
Yeah.
好啊
Wow!
哇嗷
That is one incredibly versatile hole.
这洞的用途真是让人难以置信
You're tellin' me.
可不是吗
From that moment on, everything was completely different.
自此 翻天覆地的变化发生了
No two ways about it.
并且没办法解决
Oh, I'll be back.
我马上回来
Not that we didn't try.
我们也不是没有试过
Got it.
知道了
And if one made it difficult,
一个孩子我们还可以勉强搞定
two made it almost impossible.
两个就实在无能为力了
Honey,
甜心
let's try to have sex next weekend
下周我妈来做午饭时
when my mom comes over for lunch, okay?
我们再试试滚床单吧 好吗
I'm gonna do you like a fucking...
我要把你榨干
Now, do you remember the last time
现在 你还记不记得
your husband saw you naked?
你老公上一次见你裸体是什么时候
- Jay. - Yeah.
- Jay - 什么
I need a little help here.
我需要帮助
I may be late for my thing if I don't get in here
你再不出来我就要迟到了
and take a shower right away. Can we switch places?
我现在就要洗澡 能换个位置吗
You know, don't even think about it.
真是不敢回想
The big question is, how the hell do you get it back?
最大的问题是 怎么回到过去
【随便字幕组】
爱爱上云端
All right, guys! Let's get goin'!
伙计们 咱们走
翻译：王某人 脸大了一圈的天天 四元阿汤
Clive, if you wanna wear your uniform, you gotta get changed, bud.
Clive 快点换校服
翻译： 没有分配到敏感词的阿夙 未未 节操散尽阿莫莫
Uh, one minute. This is really important.
再给我一分钟 我在干大事
What are you workin' on?
校对：小新
你在干嘛
It's my video yearbook presentation
我在做电子毕业册
for graduation on Monday.
星期一要交
That is super impressive, man.
后期：在捂脸的阿莫莫
太酷了
Where'd you learn how to do that? It's really easy, Dad.
-你竟然会做 -这很简单的 爸爸
Hey, save it as something
压制：四元阿汤
保存的时候
other than "Video 1" for me, will ya?
把视频1改成其他名字吧
It's fine. It's Video 1.
视频1很好啊
Hey, Clive. I asked you to do something, right?
嘿 Clive就当是我求你的
Don't condescend to me.
搞得好像你很和蔼一样
It's time to go to school. I'll meet you in the car.
要上学了 车上见
Nell, are you ready?
Nell 你准备好了吗
Later.
马上
All right, gang! Let's go!
-亲爱的 等等- 我们走
Wait, honey. Hold on!
等等亲爱的
I'm going!
我走啦
I'm going, too!
我也走啦
Mommy packed me two kinds of sandwiches. Jelly and peanut butter.
妈妈给我带了两种三明治 果冻的和涂了花生酱的
Oh, yes, honey. Wow.
好的甜心
Bye, honey. Good luck with your game.
宝贝再见 比赛加油
Good luck at work! Thanks, baby.
努力工作 谢谢亲爱的
Clive, buckle up your sister, will ya?
Clive 给妹妹系好安全带
Honey, did you pack all of her stuff? Yeah, yeah, of course.
-亲爱的 所有东西都带好了吗 -嗯 都带好了
Don't forget to stop by and grab...
不要忘了顺路买
Light bulbs. I am on top of it. Hey.
灯泡 我记住了
It's gonna go great.
一切都会好的
God, is this actually happening?
天呐 简直不敢相信
Am I gonna sell the blog for money? Like, real money?
我真的要卖了我的博客来赚钱吗 为了钱
Is that possible?
这可能吗
It would be amazing. For everything.
一切都会好的
Dad, I can't be late again!
爸爸 我不想再迟到了
- Yes! I'll be right there, guys! - Let's go!
- 好的我马上就来 - 快出发吧
Yes, Clive! I heard...
好的 Clive 我马上来
Is it just me or is the big one becoming kind of a dick?
怎么了是我有什么问题吗
Don't say that. Seriously, babe.
宝贝 不要这么说 真的
No, I'm just sayin' he's acting like a dick.
不 他太粗鲁
Don't say that.
别这么说
Hey, we should have sex sometime soon.
我们偶尔也该滚个床单
Oh, I would love that. Yeah, me, too.
-我也想那样 -是的 我也想啊
Maybe Thursday.
或许星期四可以
Fantastic. 'Cause it feels like it's been a long time.
太棒了 听起来还有一个世纪那么久
- It has, right? - Yeah.
- 是吗 - 对
The last time was when we got those towels from Bed Bath & Beyond.
上次滚床单还是去Bed Bath & Beyond买毛巾的时候
Oh, that's right. That was a while ago. Yeah, the linen sale.
-挺长一段时间之前了 -对 那会儿毛巾在打折
Look, we can't talk about this right now,
现在我们不能讨论这些
because we both have someplace to be.
因为我们有不同的地方要去
Not the right time. Gotta get goin'.
时机不对 我要走了
It's just been so hard to find the moment with the kids.
和孩子在一起的时候我们找不到时机
At the end of the day, we're just both so exhausted.
一天结束后我们又都太累了
You know? Oh, just tell me about it.
让我来告诉你
Maybe one of these nights, we'll have sex
或许就在这几天 我们可以滚床单
instead of watching Project Runway.
而不是看Project Runway
We'll TiVo Project Runway.
我们可以把它录下来
That's probably why they invented TiVo.
不然发明录播机干嘛
So people could have sex.
然后人们就可以滚床单了
Daddy? I still don't get it.
-爸爸 我还是不懂
Why do we keep having all of these days?
我们为什么
And then, going to bed at night?
日复一日的这样活着
And then, having all of these days?
早上起床
And then, going to bed at night?
晚上睡觉
Well, uh, that's sort of what life is.
嗯 这可能是生活的一个模式
When will it end?
它什么时候会停止
It won't.
永远不会
Well, it'll end when we die.
或许我们死的时候这一切就会停止了
Don't do that, buddy. Okay?
别这么说好吗
Won't I get bored of doing this stuff
我会厌倦生活吗
again and again and again?
不停的循环
No.
不会
But you and Mommy are bored.
但你和妈妈就厌倦了啊
Well, that's what happens with marriage.
这仅限于婚姻 无关生活
Who are you?
谁让你说话了
Dad, Nell's doing it again.
爸爸 Nell又来了
Hey. Nell, get your finger out of your butt.
Nell 把你的手指从屁股底下拿出来
Is anyone gonna clean her finger?
谁给她洗洗手指
Hey! Stop! No!
停下来别碰我
- Nell! - No. stop.
- Nell - 别碰我
Do you mind if I join you?
要我帮忙吗
I don't mind!
不要
No! Stop. Stop!
不 停下 停下
As you know, Piper Brothers is the world's number one
如你所知 派普兄弟是世界著名的
toy and child product brand
玩具盒婴儿用品品牌
in the zero-to-four age range
专为零至四岁的小孩设计
for over 50 years.
它的成立已经超过五十年了
We're looking to bring Piper Brothers into the future.
我们现在要展望派普兄弟的未来
And a big part of that is developing
其中很大一部分是发展
the Piper Brothers online community
派普兄弟网络社区
in a way that's befitting of the Piper Brothers name.
虽然是以派普兄弟的名头获利
But also in a way that says,
但也同样宣称
"This is not your grandfather's Piper Brothers."
这是与你父辈所认识的老古董派普兄弟不同的
But in order for us to do that, we need content.
但这么做的话需要我们获取一些实质内容
Hey, everybody! Annie!
嘿 大家好 Annie
Hi. Hank Rosenbaum.
-你好 -我是Hank Rosenbaum.
Such a pleasure. Thank you so much.
我的荣幸 太谢谢你了
I've heard so much about you.
我听说了很多关于你的事
Please, sit down. Thank you.
-快请坐 -谢谢
Can I get you anything? Coffee? Finger sandwich?
你要吃点什么吗 咖啡 还是手指三明治
Sliced pineapple?
还是菠萝
No, no. I'm fine with just water. Thanks.
我只喝水就好了 谢谢
Oh, well, I just wanna stick my head in and say hi
好吧 我只是想问个好
and to tell you that I'm a big fan of what you do.
然后告诉你我是你的大粉丝
Thanks. That's really nice to hear.
谢谢 听你这么说很愉快
We think you have brand potential.
我们认为你有潜在的品牌价值
The model Piper Brothers mother.
派普兄弟的母亲形象代言人
We really believe in you.
我们相信你
And I always say that belief
我总是认为
is the only metric that matters.
信任是唯一的衡量标准
We didn't bring you here to wow you with incredible numbers
我们没有用庞大的数字糊弄你
because numbers are really just
因为数字是用来
an algorithm for passion and values.
算钱的
It's like I was telling my wife, Schlomit,
就像我告诉我的妻子 Schlomit
I think I found the voice of Piper Brothers' values.
我认为我找到了能描述出派普兄弟价值的声音
Yeesh!
喔噢
Thanks!
谢谢
Are you sure we can't get you
你确定你不用来点儿
a finger sandwich or a slice of pineapple?
手指三明治或是菠萝吗
I'm okay.
不用了
There are certain content guidelines we'd like to discuss.
我们还要谈论一切特定的路线
Oh, how do you mean? Little things.
-什么意思 -只是些小事情
"Do you remember the first time
还记得
"your husband saw you naked?"
还记得你和丈夫第一次滚床单吗
Right, um...
这个
"The erections? Do you remember the erections?"
勃起 你还记得吗
No, I remember that part.
我想起来了
"Erections everywhere."
他在任何地方都能勃起
That's an unusual post for me.
我只是偶尔写那样的文章
It's a great post. I enjoyed it.
那篇博文很棒 我很爱看
But what we're looking for from you
但我们想从你这儿听到的
is your authentic, wholesome voice.
是真诚健康的声音
It's the kind of content that Piper Brothers
这才是派普兄弟的妈妈顾客们
mothers are so hungry for.
最想知道的
Look, I love being a mother.
我觉得当母亲很开心
And I love writing about it.
我也喜欢写出作为一个母亲我的感受
Well, we will make you a meaningful proposal.
我们会给你一个好的模板
And we're very excited.
期待你更好的作品
Should we have some pineapple?
是不是要吃些菠萝庆祝一下
We can have someone get you some pineapple.
我们可以让人给你拿一些
Band's coming to the Los Angeles area tomorrow.
乐队明天就要来洛杉矶了
Meantime, here's the new single. It's called Spank Me.
这是他们的最新单曲 Spank Me
I swear to you, man.
我敢向你发誓
I think I am in love with this girl.
我和这女孩坠入爱河了
Max, that's big news. Yeah.
-那可真不得了 -对
It's, like, we...
怎么说呢
I don't know. We just connect.
我也不知道 我们就这么紧密地连接在了一起
Like, we have these really long, like,
我们有着意味深长
super intense conversations. You know?
亲密的对话 你知道吗
About religion, and snowboarding.
信仰啦 滑板啦
And then, like, out of nowhere,
然后 没有预兆的
she'll just text me her boobs.
她给我发了一张她奶的照片
She just texted you a picture of her boobs out of the blue?
她奶的照片？
Oh, buddy. Good for you.
挺不错的嘛
Enjoy this time. Thank you, dude.
-好好享受 -谢谢兄弟
That's amazing. Yeah.
-太疯狂了 -是啊
I once sent Annie a picture of my dick.
我有次给Annie发了我小伙伴的照片
She was at a PTA meeting. It was horrible.
那时候她在开家长会 太可怕了
Did you go full dick?
你勃起了
Yeah. I...
是的 我..
Oh.
噢
For a man, I feel like it's dick or...
作为一个男人 我觉得小伙伴
That's kind of your only option.
是你唯一的选择
Yeah, I avoid my dick.
我就不会这么做
I usually just do, like,
我通常
you know, the sexier parts of me.
会展示我更性感的部分
Um, like, part bag, part leg.
比如 一部分蛋蛋和腿
You know?
你知道吗
I'll go undercarriage. So...
我会不举 所以
I'll have my friend, Doug, come over
我会叫我的朋友Doug过来
and we'll just knock it out real fast.
然后我们很快拍下它
Your friend comes over and takes a picture of your balls?
你的朋友会来拍你蛋蛋的照片
Yeah. Yeah. You know Doug, right?
-嗯 -你认识Doug对吗
Your neighbor? Yeah.
-你的邻居 -是的
He's actually a really good photographer.
事实上他是个很好的摄影师
He works from home.
他在外面工作
- And, so... - Hey, guys.
- 所以 - 嘿 伙计们
Hey, Rosie. Hello, Rosie.
-嘿 Rosie -你好Rosie.
New iPads are here.
你的新Ipad
Ah, thank you. I have been waiting for these.
谢谢 我等了很久了
How many of those things do you have?
你有几个
Two at a time.
两个
One for new music. One for back catalogue.
一个用来听最近的音乐 一个用来听怀旧歌曲
I have this complicated syncing system, but it works out.
同时用两个确实有些麻烦 但很实用
Well, what do you do with the old ones? I just give 'em as gifts.
-那旧的这个怎么办 -当做礼物送给他们好了
Hey, babe. How'd it go? They wanna buy it!
-宝贝 怎么样了 -他们想把我的博客买下来
That's amazing! What did they say? Did they make an offer?
太棒了 他们说什么了 是他们主动请求的吗
They're going to.
他们要
They said it would be "meaningful." Whatever that means.
他们说博客会变得意义重大 谁知道呢
I think that means a lot of money.
那意味着我们会赚很大一笔钱
- Right? - I know!
-是吗 -没错
Well, we have to celebrate.
我们要好好庆祝一下
Slow down. They haven't made the offer yet.
等等 他们还没说具体数字
They're going to. And that's reason to celebrate.
他们会的 这就是庆祝的理由
I can get Sam to cover me tonight. What do you wanna do?
我今晚要去接Sam 你要做什么
I don't know. Should we take the kids somewhere fun?
不知道 要带孩子去哪儿玩吗
Like pizza and roller skating or something?
带他们去吃披萨或者玩滑板
Totally! I can't wait.
好啊 我等不及了
I'll see you in a couple hours.
几个小时候见
Okay, hon. Love you.
好的 亲爱的 我爱你
- Hello? - Hey, Mom.
- 喂 -嗨 妈妈
What's wrong, honey?
怎么啦宝贝
Nothing's wrong.
没事
What are you doing tonight?
你今晚有什么事要干吗
All right,
好吧
who's ready for some roller skating?
谁想去玩滑板
Annie?
Annie
Clive? Nelly?
Annie, you here?
Annie, 你在这儿吗?
All right.
好吧
Hello.
你好呀
Hey-
嘿！
Hey, babe. Hi.
-嘿，宝贝  -嗨
Where are the kids?
孩子们去哪儿了？
They're at my mom's.
他们在我妈妈家
Oh, they are? I thought that we were gonna go down to the...
噢，是吗？我本来以为我们要下去……
Whoa, holy shit! Wow!
哇喔，天啊！喔！
Hi.
嗨
Wow. Look at you.
喔！看看你
Too much? No, it's great.
-太过了吗？-不，太棒了
I was thinking...
我想……
Yeah! Yes!
耶！好的！
The kids, um, how long are they...
孩子们，额，他们会呆多久在……
They're sleepin' over.
他们会在那儿过夜
Yes!
好的！
'Cause I was thinking that... Whoa.
-因为我原本想……  -哇哦
Maybe we could celebrate, just the two of us.
或许我们可以两个人单独庆祝
I get it.
我懂的
That's a great idea.
这主意棒极了
This is, like, the best idea you've ever had.
它就像是你想到过的最棒的主意
You look amazing.
你看上去美呆了
Do you own these underwear? Mm-hmm.
-这些是你的内衣吗？ -嗯哼
'Cause I've never seen those before.
因为我之前从来没有看到过它们
Come on.
来吧
This is so exciting. I'm so excited right now.
这太让人兴奋了，我现在无比兴（性）奋
And now you're on the bed.
并且你现在躺在床上
This is great. I love where this is headed.
这太棒了，我爱接下来要发生的事情
Your narrating, it's so hot.
你叙述的真是太火辣了
She said, encouragingly.
她鼓励地说道
Get over here and take these roller skates off of me.
到这儿来然后帮我脱掉溜冰鞋
I love it when you talk that way about your roller skates.
我喜欢你说起溜冰鞋的方式
Double knot.
打了两个结
Okay-
很好
Here, maybe...
这儿，或许……
No, no, no, I got it. Okay.
-不不不，我能解开它 -好的
Ooh.
噢——
Okay, that should do it.
好了，接下来应该解决它了
And a-one... Uh-huh.
-一…… -啊哈
Ow!
噢！
Fuck! Ow. Ow!
-卧槽！嗷！-嗷！
That got a lot less hot real quick, didn't it?
整件事很快就变得没那么火辣了不是吗？
Mmm.
哎……
Mm-hmm? Mm-hmm.
-嗯哼？ -嗯哼
Mm-hmm. Should we continue?
-嗯哼  -我们该继续吗？
Yes. Mm.
-是的  -嗯
Mm! Oop...
-嗯！噢……
Babe. That was like... Toothy.
-宝贝，那感觉像是……  -撞到牙齿了
Okay, just relax. Do I not seem relaxed?
-好吧，只是放松一下  -我看上去不放松吗？
No, I mean both of us. What I'm talking about.
不，我说的是指我们两个人
Oh. We'll both relax. We'll just relax.
-噢，我们都要放松  -我们只要放松
If we both relaxed, it'd be good.
如果我们都放松了，这会很好的
Just...
只是……
Sorry. I'm sorry.
抱歉，我很抱歉
What is happening with us right now? I don't know.
-刚刚我们怎么了？  -我不知道
I just got in my head a little bit.
我脑海里只是有点……
It was just weird for a second. I'm sorry. Okay, it's fine.
-某一瞬间这只是有点奇怪，我很抱歉  -好的，这没事
Here's what we're gonna do.
这是我们接下来要做的
All right. Here we go.
-好了  -我们开始吧
Let's do this thing. It's on.
-让我们做这件事吧 -它已经开始了
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
-嗯哼 -嗯哼
Oh.
噢
What? We have hit boob.
-怎么了？  -我们已经袭胸了
We've got a man on second base.
我们已经上二垒了
It's a baseball term but it also means touching your boob.
这是个棒球术语但这也指我摸着你的胸部
I know what it means. Why don't we go to third.
我知道它是什么意思，为什么我们不上三垒呢？
Whoa.
哇哦
What? Hmm?
-怎么了？  -恩？
What?
怎么了？
Too much in my own head.
太多东西在我脑袋里了
I think I've been dreaming
我想我已经梦想着
about this moment for so long Mm-hmm.
这一刻很长时间了
When we could, like, drop everything Yeah.
-就像当我们能够放下一切事情 -耶
And just properly schtup. Right, right.
-然后只是适当地滚床单 -是的是的
Instead of when you're like, half conscious
而不是当你像是心不在焉
and can't resist, you know?
无法抵抗，你知道吗？
You think I wanna resist?
你认为我想抗拒？
Of course I know that you wanna have sex.
我当然知道你想滚床单
Sometimes I just wonder if you wanna have sex that much.
只是有时我想知道你是不是想滚那么多次
I do. I do wanna have sex that much.
是的，我的确想滚那么多次
But sometimes I just feel like
但有时我只是觉得
you know, you're tired or you're stressed out.
你很疲惫或是精疲力尽了，你知道的
And maybe... Me?
-并且或许……  -我？
I don't know, I wonder sometimes
我不知道，有时我想知道
if you're still, you know, attracted to me.
你是否仍然被我吸引
Are you kidding? You're a fuckin' sexpot.
你在开玩笑吗？你是个该死的超级性感的女人
You think I'm a sexpot?
你认为我很性感？
Instant boner.
瞬间勃起
That's what I always say about you.
这就是我经常如何提起你
My wife, instant boner-giver.
我的妻子是瞬间勃起的制造者
Tell me more about this boner of yours.
告诉我更多关于你的勃起的事情
He's a good guy.
他是个好家伙
Proud. Strong. Ooh.
-隆起而又强壮 –噢
Great sense of humor.
有强大的幽默感
Let's go fuck on the kitchen floor.
让我们去厨房地板上做吧
There he is.
他就在那儿
You comin'?
你来吗？
I'm so glad that I mopped yesterday.
我很高兴昨天我拖了地
Yeah, totally.
耶，完全同意
Honey? Babe, babe, honey.
-甜心？  -宝贝，宝贝，甜心
Do you wanna go somewhere else?
你想去其他地方吗？
Oh, my God, thank God you said something.
噢，我的老天，感谢上帝你说了
My knees hurt, like, really bad. Oh, God.
-我的膝盖疼得厉害  -噢，上帝
They really hurt.
他们真的很疼
I know. My tailbone is killing me
我知道，我的尾椎骨快疼死我了
and I can see my to-do list.
并且我能看到我的待办事项了
Should we try the couch? Yeah.
-我们去尝试下沙发？ -耶
- Sex on the couch, of course, yeah. - Let's go.
-沙发上的性爱，当然了，耶-我们走吧
Let's go.
我们走
It'll just be a minute. Okay.
-只要一分钟 -好的
Oh .
噢
No. No?
-没有 -没有？
Do you have allergies?
你过敏了吗？
Yeah, all week. I've had allergies all week.
是的，整个星期，我过敏了整个星期
It's 'cause of the pressure change. Oh, is that what it is?
-这是因为压力的改变 -噢，这就是原因吗？
Mmm.
嗯
This used to totally work, remember? Totally work.
-这过去总是有用的，记得吗？ -完全有用
This was like my move.
这就像我的律动
You loved this.
你爱这样
Shit, man!
卧槽
What is happening? It's okay.
-发生什么了？ -没事的
Is it possible that we have somehow
有没有可能我们已经不知怎么
forgotten how to have sex?
忘记了怎么做爱？
Do not say that. Because we used to be great at this.
别这么说，因为我们过去很擅长这个
Yeah, we were. We were.
是的，的确，我们过去的确很擅长
I was like Shaquille O'Neal in the sack.
我就像在袋子里的Shaquille O'Neal/正在抱摔的Shaquille O'NealI was like Shaquille O'Nealin the sack.
Shaquille O'Neal：前美国NBA联盟的职业篮球运动员， 被普遍认为是联盟历史中最伟大的长人中锋球员之一
I had that kind of game.
我有过那样的比赛
What? Shaquille O'Neal's a weird comparison.
什么？Shaquille O'Neal是个奇怪的比喻
I'm just trying to say that I was a dominant player. Yeah, I know.
-我只是试着说我是个主导球员 –是的，我知道
I would've gone with Derek Fisher for you. Derek Fisher?
-我会为你变成Derek Fisher   - Derek Fisher?
Derek Fisher：前美国NBA职业篮球运动员，场上位置为控球后卫
What? He's a great player. Okay.
-怎么了？他是个伟大的球员  -好吧
I feel like we're tryin' to say the same thing. Okay.
-我觉得我们正试着说相同的事情 –好吧
You were like LeBron James. Oh, thanks, honey.
-你过去像是LeBron James  -噢，谢谢 ，甜心
LeBron James：职业篮球员，2009－2013年五年内赢得4次NBA最有价值球员
We were like Derek Fisher and LeBron James having sex.
我们过去像是和Derek Fisher与LeBron James一样滚床单
I'm saying we were world-class.
我是说我们是世界级水平的
And now, what is happening?
而现在，发生什么了？
I don't know. I mean, we're older.
我不知道，我是指我们变老了
We're parents.
我们成为了父母
Yeah, but we're not dead!
是的，但我们还没死
I still think about sex all the time.
我仍然时刻想着性爱
I know. I use your computer.
我知道，我用过你的电脑
Oh, the porn. Yeah.
噢，那些小黄片
You and I used to watch porn together all the time.
你和我过去总是一起看它
I still watch porn every once in a while.
我仍然时不时地看
You do? Yeah.
-你仍然？ -是的
But the quality of writing has really gone downhill.
但作品的质量真的在走下坡路
I like it best when it feels like they're really in love.
当里面的主角好像真的相爱时我最喜欢它
Yeah, I feel like we're getting different things out of porn.
耶，我觉得我们从小黄片里得到了不同的东西
Maybe.
或许吧
I just watch it for the naked women having sex.
我只是为了看赤裸的女人滚床单而看它
And the porn guys
但那些男优
don't get in the way or anything?
没有妨碍你或者其他什么？
Don't even see 'em.
我甚至都没有看到他们
They're completely invisible to me.
他们对我来讲完全是透明的
Should we watch some porn?
我们该看些小黄片吗？
Eh.
呃
Just feels kind of depressing.
只是觉得有点沮丧
Yeah.
是的
Do we have any of that tequila left?
我们还有哪怕一点龙舌兰酒吗？
tequila: 龙舌兰酒，是一种墨西哥产、  使用龙舌兰草的心为原料所制造出的含酒精饮品
That's a good idea. That's a really good idea. JAY: Right.
-这是个好主意，这真的是个好主意  -是的
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
好的，这就是我们接下来要做的
We are gonna drink some tequila. Whoo!
我们要和些龙舌兰酒，哇哦
We're gonna pull ourselves
我们要把自己拖出
out of this sad little moment
这正在经历的
that we're having and after that...
悲伤小瞬间，在这之后
We're gonna be Derek Fisher and LeBron fucking James.
我们将会成为Derek Fisher和LeBron fucking James.
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
这正是我们接下来要做的
I'm gonna call my mom and make sure
我会打电话给我妈妈确保
the kids went to sleep okay.
孩子们好好睡着
♪ Karma-karma-karma-karma karma chameleon
? Karma-Karma-Karma-Karma Karma Chameleo（变色龙）?
♪ She come and goes
? 她来了又走?
♪ She come and go-o-o-oes
?她来了又走——?
♪ Karma Chameleon gonna...♪
? Karma Chameleon将要?
Hey-
嘿
Oh, yeah. I just got that today.
噢，耶，我今天刚得到那个
I'm super excited about it.
我对这个东西超级兴奋
It's got a higher-resolution display,
它有更高分辨率的显示屏
which means more pixels,
意味着更多的像素
and they upgraded the camera.
并且他们升级了相机
What? I just had this idea.
-怎么了？ -我刚刚有了个想法
Oh, all right. Let's hear it.
噢，好的，让我们来听听
Let's make a porn.
让我们来制作一部小黄片吧
Excuse me?
抱歉？
Let's video ourselves having sex.
让我们来拍自己滚床单的录像
Absolutely. Yeah, totally. Really?
-绝对的，耶，当然了 –真的吗？
Yeah. The more I think about it, yes, that's a great idea.
是的，我想到了更多，没错，这是个好主意
I think it's kind of hot, right?
我想它有点火辣，对吗？
Babe, I think that is a great idea.
宝贝，我认为这是个棒极了的主意
Here, cheers.
来吧，干杯
Look at us. Annie and Jay.
Look at us.看看我们，Annie和Jay.
Send the kids off to Grandma's house,
把孩子们送到了外婆家
make a little porn.
然后拍一部小黄片
Mazel tov. To porn.
-庆祝-为了小黄片
Chug it.
快喝
I mean, drink to that.
我是指，为它干杯
Oh, yeah.
噢，耶
We don't even have to watch it if we don't want to.
如果我们不想我们甚至都不用看它
Or we could. Either way.
或者我们可以看，都可以
Okay, honey,
好的，甜心
what's our storyline?
我们的故事情节是什么？
Story? Yeah.
-故事？ -是的
I'm not sure the story's that important. Yeah.
-我不确定故事有那么重要 –耶
Oh, come on.
噢，拜托
I have another idea.
我有另一个主意了
Well, I would like to hear that idea.
好的，我想听那个主意
Because you're clearly in the zone.
因为明显你很专注
This is it.
就是它
This is what we're gonna do.
这就是我们将要做的
The Joy of Sex.
《性爱圣经》
The Joy of Sex: 《性爱圣经》，作者Alex Comfort， 于1972年出版，2008年9月更新再版，在1972~1974年间位居纽约时报畅销书榜榜首11周，并名列前5超过70周
We still have that.
它仍然还在
Every position, right now.
每个姿势，立刻马上
Oh, I like that. I like that a lot.
噢，我喜欢这主意，我太喜欢它了
Every single one?
每一个？
Yep. We're not gonna skip one.
是的，我们不会跳过任何一个
Even, uh... Yeah. Even that.
-甚至是，额…… -是的，甚至是那个
Yes! But also...
-太棒了！ -但也包括……
Totally. It's in the book.
当然，它在这本书里
Yay! And we'll video the whole thing.
耶！并且我们会录下整件事情
You're a genius. No, I married a genius.
你是个天才，不我娶了个天才
I need another drink.
我需要再喝杯酒
I need to be drunker.
我需要变成醉汉
Okay-
好的-
- Here I go. - Get here. Okay.
-我在这儿了 –到这儿来，好的
Action.
开始
Hello. Hi.
-哈喽 –嗨Hi.
And welcome to Annie and Jay's,
欢迎来到Annie和Jay的家
A Night With Annie and Jay.
和Annie与Jay的一夜
I'm Jay and this is my lovely wife, Annie.
我是Jay，这是我可爱的妻子Annie.
And tonight,
而今晚
we intend to demonstrate every position
我们想要演示每个
in The Joy of Sex.
在《性爱的乐趣》里的体位
Are you speaking to our students, honey?
你在和我们的学生说话吗，甜心？
Why, yes, l am, Annie.
是的，Annie.
And this is our dojo.
而这是我们的训练场
Our sex dojo.
我们的性爱训练场
Our sex dojo. That's right.
我们的性爱训练场，没错
Annie, the book, please.
Annie, 请把书拿来
Here you go, Professor.
给你，教授
Thank you, Annie.
谢谢 Annie.
Well.
好的
Wow. Wow. Okay.
哇哦哇哦，好的
Look at that bush.
看看那浓密的毛发
Well, look at his bush.
看看他浓密的毛发.
I'm talking about his bush.
我就是在说他的毛发
Is that still his bush?
那还是他的吗？
I can't tell where her bush ends and his begins.
我都分不清哪些是她的哪些是他的了
People were furrier in the '70s.
在70年代人们都是皮毛商
Oh.
噢
"Matrimonial." Mm-hmm. That's right. Wow. Hmm.
-“婚姻”（体位），嗯哼 –没错，哇哦，嗯哼
Matrimonial.
“婚姻”Matrimonial.
Can we start with something other than missionary?
我们能从传教士体位以外的开始吗？
Missionary Position: 传教士体位即男上位，是指男性位置于另一人上方的性交体位。之前提到的Matrimonial同样也是指该体位
Absolutely. We can loop back around to missionary.
当然，我们可以循环之后回到传教士体位
Right. It's not goin' anywhere.
没错，它不会去其他地方
Okay, close your eyes, my dear.
好的，闭上你的眼睛，亲爱的
Say "stop" when I... Stop!
-说“停”，当我……  -停！
"Flanquette."
铁塔式（我猜的）"Flanquette."
Flanquette! Oh.
-铁塔式 –噢Flanquette!
That is what I'm talkin' about.
这就是我说的
I feel good about this one. Me, too.
-我感觉这个不错 –我也是
Okay. So you see what's happening?
好的，所以你知道怎么做吗？
That's my leg. Yeah, okay.
-那是我的腿 –耶，好的
But that's your leg. Okay.
-这是你的腿 –好的
So, it's like...
所以这就像……
Yep. All right.
耶，好的
Let's do this. Let's do it. Let's do it.
-让我们来完成这个吧 –让我们来尝试下 –让我们来完成它
What?
怎么了？
- Come here. Come here. - Okay, here we go.
-过来，过来 –好的，我们开始吧
Hi. Hi.
-嗨 –嗨
Okay, ready? Okay. Yeah.
-准备好了吗？好的 –是的
Go. Go.
-开始 –开始
You're amazing at that.
你太棒了
Really?
真的吗？
Oh, my gosh. Still?
-噢，我的老天 –依旧？
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑嘛
You were like a machine.
你就像台做爱机器
Like a battering ram.
像攻城槌
Thank you.
谢谢
Honey? Yeah?
-甜心？ -耶？
Erase that video, okay?
把视频删了，好吗？
Yeah.
好的
I don't want the kids to ever, ever, ever, ever, ever...
我不想让孩子们……
No, I'll erase it. No worries.
不，我会删了它的，别担心
You don't forget, okay?
你不会忘记的，对吗？
I won't forget.
我不会忘记的
I love fucking you.
我爱艹你
I fucking love you.
艹，我爱你
No! No, not my own son!
不！不，不要是我自己的儿子
Whoops!
噢！
So as long as we get them both down
只要我们在凌晨两点让他们
for thew second naps by 2:00 - ish,
睡上第二觉
then the nighttime is a little better.
那么晚上就会变得美好一点
Yeah, if we don't get them down by 2:00-ish we're totally fucked.
是的，如果我们不让他们在两点睡着我们就完了
Wow. "Totally fucked." That's nice.
哇哦，完蛋了，真好
This is just an expression.
这只是一种表达
How else would you describe this?
你还会用其他什么来描述这个？
I would describe this as...
我会把它说成……
Super fucked? ...a gift of life. You're welcome.
-超级糟糕？-来自生活的礼物，不用谢
You guys are bouncing the shit out of those babies.
你们要把宝宝摇出祥了
You're bouncing 'em hard.
你们摇他们摇的太用力了
Oh, you guys are doing great.
噢，你们做的真是太棒了
It's getting a lot easier, though.
这样它会变得简单许多
Oh, we're seeing the light at the end of the tunnel.
噢，我们看到了隧道尽头的曙光
Yeah. You guys should have seen us a month ago.
-是的 –你们应该看看我们一个月前的样子
I don't even know who I was then.
那时候我都忙得不知道自己是谁
Oh, my God. These are the salad days.
哦，上帝啊，现在简直就是最佳时期
Yeah, it sounds really intense, but you got it!
是的，那听上去的确很糟糕，但你们搞定它了！
So, are you guys thinking of having more?
所以你们有想要更多的孩子吗？
No.
不
Isn't it crazy that the boys
那些即将毕业的四年级男孩们是不是很疯狂？
are graduating fourth grade? Isn't that crazy?
是不是很疯狂？
And Howard is graduating fifth grade. When did that happen?
而Howard五年级了，那什么时候会发生？
Since when did kids graduate from fourth and fifth grade?
当孩子们从四、五年级毕业了？
It used to be school just ended.
过去的学校毕业就只是毕业了
There wasn't a ceremony for everything.
不是所有事都有典礼仪式
Just... Ignore him.
-只是……  -无视他
- I will. - Yeah.
-我会的 –没错-
I love your blog, by the way.
话说我爱你的博客
Oh, thank you.
噢，谢谢
Hey, do you think Piper Brothers is gonna go for it?
嘿，你认为派普兄弟会去看它吗？
Fingers crossed. Yes.
-上帝保佑 -太棒了
Hey. good people.
嘿，大家
Hi, honey. Hi.
嗨，甜心，嗨
Hello, you. Hi.
你好呀，嗨
You're really wet. Look at you.
你真的很湿，看看你
Yeah. I should go put on some dry clothes.
是的，我该去换点干衣服了
Oh, um, I'm gonna, uh, come with you
噢，额，我和你一起去
'cause we gotta talk about that... About, uh...
因为我们要讨论一下……关于，额……
The thing. Yes, the thing.
-那件事 –对，那件事
Totally. We have to talk about a thing.
当然，我们得讨论一件事
Thank you.
谢谢
Jesus. Kill me.
耶稣啊，杀了我吧
Hey. Hello, pal.
嘿，哈喽伙计
Gentlemen. Hey, Howie.
-男士们 –嘿，Howie
It's Howard.
我的名字是Howard.
Just Howard.
叫我 Howard就好
Sorry.
抱歉
You know what? I just gave up a Super Soaker.
你知道吗？我刚刚放弃了一把
Super Soaker:水枪品牌，创立于1982年
Why don't you get in there, bud?
你为什么不参与进去，伙计？
Oh! Hmm.
-噢！ -嗯
Maybe I will. Yeah.
-或许我会的 –耶
I do enjoy Super Soakers.
我的确很喜欢Super Soakers
Yeah!
耶！Yeah!
You can see the difference in personalities already.
你现在已经能看出孩子们性格的不同
This one loves watermelon.
这个喜欢西瓜
This one's kind of an asshole.
这个某种程度上是个混蛋
I think everyone had fun, right?
我觉得每个人都玩的很愉快，不是嘛？
Oh, totally. It was great.
噢，当然，派对很棒
What about Punit and Kia?
Punit和Kia怎么样？
Whoa!
哇哦
Kinda hate each other, right?
有点讨厌彼此，对吗？
Sure seemed like it, yeah.
似乎的确像是这样，耶
"Enjoyed your video"?
看过了你的视频？
Where's the pizza cutter?
披萨刀去哪里了？
Babe, do you see the pizza cutter out there anywhere?
宝贝，你有在外面看到披萨刀吗？
Um...
额……
Yes?
是的？
Jay.
Jay
Jay, the pizza cutter?
Jay，看到披萨刀了吗？
It's yours.
是你的啦
I have so many of them. Enjoy.
我有好多呢，希望你喜欢
Wow.
哇塞
Fuck me.
该死
Honey, are there any more plates outside?
亲爱的，外面还有盘子吗？
Just a second.
等下
Hello!
大家好！
Hi!
你们好！
Hello!
大家好！
Honey... Fuck!
-亲爱的   -卧槽！
That sweater nice, girl.
那毛衣真不错，姑娘
Thanks.
谢谢
I...
我……
Was it... Did I...
是不是……我干……
Could...
可能……
What the hell is going on?
到底发生了什么？
Um...
额……
It's, uh...
就是，额……
When...
当你……
You know the cloud?
你知道云服务吗？
So what you're saying
所以你说的是
is that instead of erasing the video like you said that you would,
你没像你保证得那样删掉录像
you actually ended up sending it
而到头来把它发给了
to everyone that you ever given
每一个以前你
one of those fucking iPads to?
送过你旧的iPad的人？
That is not at all what happened. No?
-不是这样的！ -不是?
Well, technically, yes! It's exactly what happened.
好吧，技术上是这样的，就是那么回事儿
But it was so accidental, it doesn't even qualify as...
不过这是个大意外，甚至不能把它说成……
Thank you.
谢谢你
Hank Rosenbaum!
What? The Piper Brothers guy!
-啥？ -派普兄弟的那个人！
You gave him one? Yes! I told you I needed one for work.
-你送了他一个？-对啊！我跟你说过我需要一个专门用来工作的
I put my entire presentation on it.
我把我所有的陈述都放进去了
You did?
是吗？
I'm supposed to be the model Piper Brothers mother!
我该是个模范”派普兄弟“代言人妈妈的！
Maybe he hasn't seen it yet.
可能他还没看呢！
As a matter of fact, Annie, I'm willing to bet that none of these people
事实上, Annie,我情愿打赌这些人里还没有人注意到
have even noticed that the video is on there yet.
那个录像被放在云端上了
Except for this text, but...
除了发这条短信的人，但是……
What text?
什么短信？
I received a text.
我收到了条短信
From who?
谁发的？
It's unclear.
不清楚
I'm not sure how to hurt you right now, Jay.
我都不知道现在该怎么揍你，Jay
I know.
我知道
But let's take a deep breath. Shit!
-但是让我们深吸一口气 -靠！
Come sit down next to me.
来，坐我旁边来
Come sit down. Come here.
坐下来，来这边
Let's look at
我们来理理
what's actually happened. Okay.
-到底发生了什么 -好吧
We made a video
我们拍了个
of ourselves having sex
三小时长的
for about three hours,
自拍滚床单录像
and it was amazing, right?
那感觉很赞,对吧?
Yeah, no, it was great. Okay.
-是啊，不，是超赞 -好吧
And then you asked me to erase it and I forgot.
然后你叫我删掉录像，我给忘了
You forgot? I forgot.
-你忘了？ -我忘了
And now our video
现在我们的录像
has been synced to several devices.
已经在几个设备上完成同步
All of which, though, are basically in the possession of friends.
虽然，这些设备都基本上是我们朋友们的所有物了
Oh, God. And acquaintances.
-天哪 -和熟人们
And the mailman.
还有邮差
Oh, God!
老天爷啊！
Who sent you that text, Jay?
谁发给你那条短信的，Jay？
I don't know. I don't know, Annie.
我不知道啊不知道， Annie.
Did you call the number?
你打给这人了没？
That is actually a really good idea.
这真是个好主意
Oh, my God.
哦，我天
Your call has been forwarded...
您所拨打的电话被转接到了……
Voice mail! Okay, oh.
-语音信箱！ -好吧，哦
Hi, this is Jay Hargrove.
你好，我是Jay Hargrove.
Could you give me a call back
你方便的话能不能
at your earliest convenience, please?
尽快给我回个电话？求求你
I believe you have the number. Bye.
我想你有我的号码，再见
That's it?
就这样说？
What the hell else was I supposed to say to the guy?
那我该跟这人说什么别的话？
"Who the fuck is this?"
"你他妈是谁？"
I wouldn't call back if someone left that on my machine.
要是有人这么给我留言，我可不会回电的
Okay, we have to get these iPads back right now.
好吧，我们必须现在就去要回这些Ipad
Hello?
喂？
Hi, Mom! Hi, honey.
-你好吗，妈妈！-你好啊，亲爱的
Is there any chance that you might be able
你能不能过来一下
to come and, um, watch the kids for us, uh, like, right away?
嗯，帮我们看孩子，嗯，马上过来？
Right now?
马上来?
We really need you to, like, right away
我们真的很需要你马上来看孩子
if you could come over.
如果你可以过来
Why, I suppose.
为什么？我想可以吧
- Thanks, Mom. That's so great. - Thanks. Annie.
- 谢了，妈妈，真是太好了- 谢了，Annie
Hold on a second. What?
等下。干嘛？
It might be worth asking your mom,
可能有必要让你妈妈
um, to bring her iPad.
嗯, 带上她的iPad
Are you kidding me?
你在逗我吗？
And could you bring your iPad, too?
还有你能不能也带上你的iPad？
My iPad? Yeah.
-我的iPad? -嗯哪
Okay. Great, okay.
-好吧 -太好了
What are you not gonna forget? The iPad.
-你不会忘了带什么？ -iPad啊
So say goodbye, hang up and then come right away.
那就拜拜啦，挂电话之后就马上来
Okay. All right.
好好好
Can you hang up? Okay, honey.
-你可以挂了吗？ -好的，亲爱的
Okay, hang up now, Mom.
好的，你快挂啊老妈
Okay, say goodbye.
好的，说再见
Okay, hang up.
好的，挂掉
Bye. Okay, bye!
-再见 -好的，再见！
Who else has these things?
谁还有这些iPad？
Let's think about it.
让我们来捋一捋
Robby, the mailman...
Robby, 邮差……
Every time you say "mailman," Jay,
你一说"邮差," Jay,
I'm just gonna hit you.
我就要揍你
You see, it was Christmas...
那什么，过圣诞节嘛……
I don't give a shit.
我不管
Mailman, Robby, Hank, my mother, and who else?
邮差, Robby, Hank,我妈，还有谁?
Oh, my God!
哦，我的天啊
Clive?
May I see that for a second, honey? Why?
-我能不能看一下你iPad, 亲爱的? - 为什么?
Just for a second. I was using that!
-就一下 -我在用啊
What the hell?
你干嘛啊？
I can't take any chances.
我不能冒任何风险
Okay, kid! Come on, Jay!
好了，孩子！快来，Jay！
Grandma's here for some mysterious reason!
外婆来啦，因为某个神秘的原因！
Oh, my gosh! Is that the iPad
哦，我天！那就是
I gave you? I love that iPad.
我给你的那个iPad？我可爱那只了
Can I borrow it? Why is Grandma here?
-我能借下吗？ -为什么外婆来了？
Yay! Grandma!
耶! 外婆来啦!
Okay. Grandma's gonna watch you guys
好了，外婆在你爹妈出去的时候
while Mommy and Daddy go out.
会照看你俩的
You guys can order Chinese food.
你们可以叫点中国菜吃
I hate Chinese food. Okay. Then order a pizza.
-我讨厌中国菜 -那好吧，就叫个披萨
Once again, enjoy this iPad.
再来一遍，享受这个iPad吧
I had to make sure it was working. Enjoy that.
我必须确保它没坏，玩儿去吧
Let's go! Thank you. What about my iPad?
-走吧! 谢谢你 -我的iPad呢？
Thank you.
谢谢你
Man. The construction on these things is just unbelievable.
天哪，这些iPad的构造真是惊为天人
Jay! Come on, Jay, let's go!
Jay! 快来,Jay, 走走走!
Let's go to Robby and Tess' house first! Let's go!
我们先去Robby和Tess的家！快走！
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Sorry! Got it!
耶耶耶！抱歉，拿到了
So I'm just trying to understand
我正在试着理解
why it is that you don't erase these things
你为什么不在送别人iPad之前
before you give them to people.
把所有数据都清除呢？
I have amazing playlists
我有个赞爆的播放列表
and people want them. That's the gift.
大家都想要，那才是礼物
The gift is the playlist, not the iPad.
礼物是那个播放列表而不是iPad
When I update my music library, it syncs to their iPads.
当我更新我的音乐库时，也会同步到他们的iPad上
I use an app called Frankensync to sync the playlists.
我用个叫Frankensync的应用来同步播放列表
I upgraded to this new app,
我最近升级到了这个新应用
Bride of Frankensync,
Frankensync的新娘
and now, apparently, it syncs all of my shit
然后现在，很明显它在我所有iPad上
to everywhere 'cause it's a very powerful app!
同步了我所有东西，因为这是个非常强大的应用！
How do you forget to erase your sex tape?
你怎么会忘记删掉你的性爱录像呢？
It kept slipping my mind
这事儿我一时忘记了
and then, the next thing I knew, it went up!
然后我回过神来的时候，它就上传了！
It went up to the cloud!
上传到云盘上去了！
And you can't get it down from the cloud?
你就不能把它从云上拽下来吗？
Nobody understands the cloud!
没人弄得懂云！
It's a fucking mystery!
那就是个该死的谜！
Look, all that's happened here is there's been a very
你瞧，现在发生的就是个
minor syncing mishap.
很小的因为同步而产生的灾祸
This is not minor!
一点都不小！
And I wish that you would just admit that you fucked up
我原本希望你会就此承认你搞砸了
instead of trying to convince me that this isn't a big deal
而不是在这对我唧唧歪歪说，出的不是个大事
'cause it is a big deal.
因为这就是个大事
You know what, Annie?
知道么，Annie?
I'm on there, too.
我也在录像里
Oh, who gives a shit? Nobody cares about you.
哦，谁在乎啊?没人在乎你的
Nobody wants to watch you having sex.
没人想看你滚床单的
You said it yourself. Nobody cares about the guy!
你自己说的啊，没人在意男优的！
It's the woman that has to live with it forever.
女人才能永远靠这个产业过活
Who is it? "Guess who?" Smiley face.
-谁啊？ -“你猜我谁？”笑脸
Who the fuck is this? Fuck!
-这他妈谁啊？！ -卧槽
It's gotta be Tess. It's gotta be Tess.
一定是Tess，一定是Tess
You think? Yeah!
-你觉得是他？ -对！
With the whole "XOXO smiley face" thing? Yeah. It's Tess.
会发"抱抱么么哒 笑脸" 这些的，对，就是Tess
Right, is that really a Tess thing,
对的，但就只有Tess这么发
or is that more of like a, uh, very, very common thing?
还是其实大家都会这么发？
No, it's a Tess thing.
不，就只有Tess这么发
She must just be joking around.
她一定就是跟我们开开玩笑
Except her number is in my phone so it would say, "Tess."
但是我有她的号码，发信人会写着“Tess”
Well, maybe she got a new phone.
嗯，可能她买了只新手机
She probably saw what it was
她可能看到那个录像了
and stopped watching it immediately
然后立马关掉
because she has so much respect for our privacy.
因为她非常尊重我们的隐私
This makes perfect sense.
完全说得通
Right. Okay.
对，好的
Okay, great. It's Tess.
很好, 就是Tess.
I'd buy it. Yeah.
-我信我信 -那是
She picks up the iPad, sees there's a sex tape on there,
她拿起iPad，看到上面有个性爱录像
pushes play, it's us, immediately stopped it,
点了播放，看到是我们俩拍的，就立刻暂停不看
'cause she respects us. Yes.
-因为她尊重我们 -没错
Then she went out and got a new phone and a new phone number.
然后她出去买了个新手机和新手机号
Yeah.
对
So do you think that means Robby has seen it, too?
所以你觉得那是不是意味着Robby也看了？
Well, if he's seen it, you're gonna have to get a new best friend.
嗯，如果他已经看了，你就不得不去找个新死党
We're just gonna cut Robby and Tess out of our lives?
我们要跟Robby和Tess绝交?
Yeah, that's right. And if the mailman has seen it, we're movin'.
对，没错，如果邮差看了，我们就搬走
Wait. What if it's not Tess?
等等，如果不是Tess干的怎么办?
Okay, look. We're just gonna feel this out,
好，听着，我们就去试探试探
and if it doesn't seem like it's her,
如果不像她做的
we just don't say anything at all. Okay? Of course.
-我们就什么都不说，懂了吗？ -那当然
No, no. They do not need to know about this. Okay?
不不， 他们不需要了解这件事，懂吗？
Babe, it's gonna be pretty easy
宝贝，很容易试探出来
to tell if they've seen it or not.
他们有没有看过录像的
Hey!
嘿！
Hey. Hey!
-嘿 -嘿！
What's going on?
怎么样啊?
What's going on with you?
你怎么样啊？
Nothing. Nothing. Just hanging out.
没什么没什么，就是两个人一起
It's our anniversary, actually,
其实，今天是我们的结婚纪念日
so Marta took Howard to a movie
所以Marta带Howard去看电影了
and we're just, uh,
我们两个就，嗯，
hanging out, watching some...
一起看点……
Hey! What are you guys doing here?
嘿！什么风把你们吹来了？
Hey- Hey.
-你好 -嘿
We're so sorry to drop by like this
我们很抱歉像这样突然造访
on your anniversary and all.
正巧撞上你们结婚纪念日什么的
Yeah, why didn't you guys mention it was your anniversary?
就是，你们干嘛不提一下今天是你们的结婚纪念日？
Uh, cause it's our 12th anniversary? Yeah.
-额，因为这是我们第十二个结婚纪念日？-是啊
Like, who cares, right? So...
就，没人在乎啊，是吧？所以……
You guys wanna come in?
你们想进来吗？
Or not.
还是算了？
What were you guys watching?
你们俩在看什么？
Um...
嗯……
This is really embarrassing. Yeah.
-说出来真丢脸啊 -是啊
Just tell us what you guys were watching.
告诉我们你们在看什么就好
Yeah. It's not a big deal. What were you watching?
-对啊，又不是什么大不了的事 -你们在看什么？
Okay, all right, all right.
好吧好吧
We're watching the first season of Breaking Bad.
我们在看《绝命毒师》第一季
It's really embarrassing
说出来真丢脸
how far behind we are.
我们落下了多少啊
That's a great show. Yeah.
-那是部好片 -嗯
You guys really are far behind.
你们真的落下了好多
That's all right. Don't tell us what happens!
-没什么 -别剧透！
Hey, while we're here,
嘿，既然我们都在，
remember that iPad I gave you?
还记得我给你的那个iPad吗？
Yeah. Yeah.
-嗯  -嗯
I need that back.
我要收回来
Oh, uh...
哦，嗯……
Okay. Oh, was that why you...
好吧，哦，难道这就是为什么你……
Is that why you came here
这就是你来这里的原因
to our house, to get your iPad back?
到我们家，拿回你的iPad？
Well... Um...
-这…… -嗯……
I have some stuff on it that I need.
上面有点东西我要……
What? Dirty pictures or something?
什么？黄色图片什么的？
You guys make a sex tape?
难道你们拍了个性爱录像？
Did you guys watch it?
你们看了吗？
I was kidding.
我刚刚是在说笑
What the fuck?
卧槽
And then Jay received this text that said,
然后Jay收到了条短信，写着
"Loved your video. Thanks for sharing. XOXO."
"爱你们的录像哟，感谢分享么么哒"
And you thought that was from me?
你认为是我发的？
Well, it sounded like you.
嗯，看上去像你发的
I don't think if I'd seen your sex tape, I would have done "XOXO."
我不觉得要是我看了你们的性爱录像以后，我还会发”么么哒“
I was hoping it was you...
我还希望是你……
Because if it wasn't me, then who is it?
因为如果那不是我发的，就不知道是什么牛鬼蛇神发的了？
No, I get it. I get it.
我懂我懂
Um... Could we back up for just a second?
嗯……我们能倒回去一下下吗？
So you taped yourself having sex for three hours?
你们说你们拍了自己滚3小时床单？
Yes.
对啊
Why did you do that?
你们干嘛要拍啊？
Never mind.
没事没事
Who has sex for three hours? We did.
-谁能滚3小时床单啊 -我们啊
That's the length of the movie Lincoln. You did the full Lincoln.
整整有电影《林肯》这么长的时间，你们滚完了一整部《林肯》啊
Well, guys, I'm sorry, you know,
呃，伙计们，我很抱歉，
but I'm not the one who sent that text.
但我不是发短信的那个人。
God, this isn't happening. Oh...
上帝啊，不会吧。噢……
Oh, okay, uh, who else has these things?
噢，好吧，呃，还有谁有这些东西？
You guys, the mailman...
你们，邮递员……
Hank Rosenbaum.
Hank Rosenbaum。
Piper Brothers guy? Yes!
－派普兄弟的那个人？ －对。
Oh, the guy that wants to buy your blog?
哦，那个想要买你博客的人？
And who's very concerned about my image.
并且十分关心我的形象。
Okay, I'm an idiot!
好吧，我是个蠢货！
No! Come on! You messed up.
－不！拜托！－你把一切都搞砸了！
No.
不。
He is. Let him have that.
他是。让他承担这个名号。
I would have killed you.
我会杀了你。
Oh, I mean, if you had thought about it for a second,
噢，我想说，如果你哪怕想那么一秒钟，
you'd know to just password-protect your shit.
你都会知道用密码来保护你那些乱七八糟的东西！
I would have killed you in your sleep.
我会趁你睡着了杀了你。
Or just fucking delete it.
Or just fucking delete it.或者就特么的删了它！
Oh, my God. Wait!
噢，天呐，等等！
Wait a minute! What?
－等一下！ －怎么了？
My sister is his florist!
我妹妹是他的花商！
Oh, my God, do you think she knows where he lives?
噢，老天，你认为她知道他住在哪里？
Yeah, I think she's been to his house. She's his florist!
是的，我认为她去过他的房子。她是他的花商！
Hold on. What's the plan here?
等等，现在的计划是什么？
We're just gonna show up at this guy's house?
我们就这么出现在这个人的家里？
Yeah! And we're coming with you!
当然！而且我们要和你们一起去！
Oh, my God. It'll be a fun night! We have a sitter!
噢，天呐，今晚会非常有趣！我们有人帮我们看着孩子！
I'll call Rochelle. Yeah!
－我会打电话给Rochelle。 －对！
Hey, my sister thought the every position thing was a great idea!
嘿，我妹妹认为每个体位之类的事情是一个特别好的主意。
You told your sister? What is up?
你告诉了你妹妹？发生了什么？
Big supporter of you. Well, I thought she'd be thrilled.
全力支持你。嗯，我想她会很激动的。
Hey-
嘿。
iPad.
iPad。
Yeah, yeah. Boy, what a mess.
对啊，没错，老兄，真是混乱。
No. Can I have it?
不是，能给我吗？
Huh?
啊？
The iPad. Yeah.
－那个iPad. －对。
You came over here to get it.
你到这里来就是为了拿它。
I need the iPad, please.
我需要那个ipad，拜托了。
What if I can't get it right now?
如果我现在拿不到它会怎么样？
Just give me the iPad.
就把ipad给我。
What if I just erase the video myself? Dude.
－如果我自己把视频删除了呢？ －伙计。
Okay. You're gonna have to give me all that music again.
好吧。你要把所有的音乐再给我一次。
Dude! Oh, fine! Jeez!
－伙计！ －噢，好吧！老天！
Did you just pull this out of your pants?
你刚刚是不是从你的裤子里拿出来？
Yeah.
是的。
I feel like a second ago,
我记得几秒之前，
you said you couldn't remember where it was.
你说你不记得它在那里了？
I forgot.
我忘了。
Fair enough.
真是够了。
It's an easy mistake to make. Okay.
－这真是太容易犯的错了。 －是的。
So, what are we gonna do?
那么，我们要做些什么？
Yeah. What's the plan, gang?
是的。计划是什么，伙计们？
Should we pretend we have a flat,
我们那要不要假装我们的轮胎瘪了，
and none of us had our cell phones?
然后我们都没有带手机。
We knock. You're like, "Hank! What a surprise!"
我们敲门。你们就这样，“Hank，真是太巧了！”
Yes. And then l jump in and I say,
没错，然后我跳出来说，
"Hi. I'm your florist's sister, Tess."
“嗨，我是你花商的姐姐，Tess。”
Feel like this is just
感觉这样度过你们的周年纪念日
a super weird way to spend your anniversary.
真是非常得奇怪。
For a 12th anniversary, I think it's pretty solid. ANNIE: You know what?
－这样的12周年纪念日，真是太棒了。 －你们知道吗？
You guys stay in the car. It's our mess.
你们留在车里，这是我们的过错。
We can go clean it up. Right, babe?
我们能去把它处理好的。是吗，宝贝？
I think we'd really like to be part of the plan.
我认为我们真的很想成为计划的一部分。
Let us participate.
让我们参加吧。
Guys, we're gonna be in and out up there.
伙计们，我们会去那里然后离开。
We're gonna knock on the door.
我们会去敲门。
Yes, it'll be a little awkward at first.
没错，一开始可能会有一点尴尬。
But I really think it'll be fine.
但我真的认为会没事的。
Okay, so this is what we're gonna do.
好吧，那么这是我们接下来要做的。
I'll distract him, you say you have to go to the bathroom,
我会分散他的注意力，你说你要去趟洗手间，
and then you search the house for the iPad. Good? Okay, let's go.
然后你在房子里找ipad。行吗？好，我们走。
Annie. Annie, can you hold on one second?
Annie。 Annie，你能不能等一下。
Get up here. That house is huge.
－快来。 －这个房子这么大。
We'll tell him you have diarrhea.
我们就告诉他你腹泻。
First of all, that's embarrassing.
首先，这太尴尬了。
And second of all, who tells someone that they have diarrhea?
然后其次，谁会告诉别人他们腹泻？
Food poisoning.
食物中毒。
Okay. How about I distract him and you have the food poisoning?
行。那么我来分散他的注意力，你来食物中毒如何？
Uh, no. l am not gonna have food poisoning.
呃，不。我不会食物中毒。
You're gonna have food poisoning.
你才会食物中毒。
The person who forgets to erase
忘记把性爱录音带删除的人
the sex tape has food poisoning.
才会食物中毒。
It's in the book.
书上就是这么写的。
Annie! Oh...
－Annie！ －噢……
Well, I'll be!
好吧，我来。
Hank? Hey!
Hank？嘿！
What a surprise. This is so crazy.
－真是太出乎意料了。 －这太疯狂了。
You live here?
你住在这里？
I'm sorry. I'm lost. You two know each other?
很抱歉，我听糊涂了。你们认识？
This is Hank, honey. Remember I was telling you about Hank?
这是Hank，亲爱的。还记得我跟你说的Hank吗？
Hank Rosenbaum?
Hank Rosenbaum？
Hank Rosenbaum!
Hank Rosenbaum！
This is my husband, Jay.
这是我丈夫，Jay。
Jay. The famous Jay.
Jay。那个著名的Jay。
In the flesh. It's a pleasure to meet you.
亲眼所见。见到你十分高兴。
- Likewise. - Wow!
- 我也是。 - 哇！
What a crazy coincidence, honey. Right? Wow.
真是一个疯狂的巧合，亲爱的。是不是？哇。
We were just randomly in the neighborhood.
我们只是碰巧到了这附近。
We've been knocking on doors trying to, uh,
我们敲门试图，呃，
collect money for a charity.
为慈善筹钱。
What charity?
什么慈善？
Uh, it's for, um... Charity for... For kids.
呃，是为了，呃……面向……面向孩子的慈善。
Yeah, for kids that have, um,
对，是面向那些有……
oversized...
过大的……
Kidneys. Kidneys.
肾脏的孩子。
They got these
他们有
enormous kidneys.
非常大的肾。
It's so sad.
这太让人难过了。
You have to see it. So we're just trying to help them out.
你一定要看看。所以我们想帮帮他们。
"Hey, Dad. Da.
“嘿，爸爸。爸，
"What is this bulge in me back, Da?"
我背后这个凸出的东西是什么，爸？”
"That's your kidney, son. Get on with it."
“那是你的肾，孩子。和它好好相处。”
They're, uh, British orphans.
他们是，呃，英国孤儿。
Yeah, so we're just out to try to raise some money for it.
是的，所以我们想能不能帮忙为它筹些钱。
Anyhow, would you possibly want to contribute?
无论如何，你想不想为此出一份力？
Yes. Please. Come in. I will get my checkbook.
当然，请进。我去拿我的支票本。
Thanks. That's just so generous of you.
谢谢，你真是太慷慨了。
Hey, do you think that Jay could use your bathroom?
嘿，Jay能不能用一下你的洗手间？
Because he has diarrhea. Oh.
－因为他有些腹泻。 －噢……
Food poisoning. He has the shits, as they say.
食物中毒、就像他们说得，他吃的什么乱七八糟的。
Oh, sure, it's right down the hall. Go crazy.
哦，当然，就在走廊尽头。尽情的……
Thank you.
谢谢。
Mmm.
嗯……
Oh, well, come on in and make yourself comfortable.
哦，嗯，进来吧，不要拘束。
Oh, thank you.
噢，谢谢。
Wow! It's a really lovely house.
哇！这个房子真温馨。
Oh, thank you. Put on some music.
噢，谢谢。我来放些音乐。
Sure. Wow!
好的。哇！
Shit! Fuck!
靠！卧槽！
What the fuck?
特么的？
Would you like something to drink?
你想喝些什么吗？
What?
什么？
I'm sorry. Let me turn this down so we can talk.
不好意思。我把音量调低一点这样我们就能聊天了。
Can I get you something to drink?
要我给你拿些东西喝吗？
Sure.
行啊。
Schlomit and the kids are away,
Schlomit和孩子们都不在，
so I'm just spreading my wings.
所以我能放任自己，
Drinking some scotch.
喝些苏格兰酒。
Ah.
啊.
Fifty years old. Yeah.
－50年的。 －是啊。
The good stuff.
可是好东西。
Here's to our bright future together.
为了我们共同的美好明天。
Whatever it may hold.
无论它会变成怎么。
Wow. That's a really, uh, interesting painting.
哇。那真是一幅，呃，有趣的画。
Do you like it?
你喜欢？
Yeah.
是啊。
I had it commissioned.
我有它的版权。
It's a moment from the movie The Lion King.
这是“狮子王”中的一个场景
Lion King：《狮子王》。剧中原画为巫师Rafiki为小狮子Simba行洗礼。
Except it's me in place of Rafiki.
只不过这里是我而不是Rafiki。
Rafiki：《狮子王》中荣耀国的法师，神秘的老狒狒长老。
So, that's me
所以，那是我
presenting Simba to all of the creatures
把Simba介绍给其他的动物
Simba：《狮子王》的主角，在历经千辛万苦后终成为荣耀国的国王。
from the Pride Lands to behold.
俯视着荣耀国。
Pride Lands：《狮子王》故事发生的地方。
It's beautiful.
它很美。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'm gonna put on something a little more festive.
我要放些更喜庆的东西。
Hi.
嗨。
Hey, hey, little guy.
嘿，嘿，小家伙。
Stay.
停下。
Stay!
停下！
Sit!
坐下！
You seem,
你看上去，
I don't know, nervous.
我不知道，很紧张。
It's just a little awkward showing up at your house
只不过在你家出现
and asking you for a donation, is all.
还问你要捐款很尴尬，真的。
I'm glad you're here.
我很高兴你在这里。
I could use the company.
能陪我一会儿。
Wow!
哇！
I know.
我懂的。
No, no, no! Please! No! No!
不不不！拜托！不不！
No! Stay!
不！停下！
Heel!
下去！
I was hoping that we would get a chance
我正希望我能有机会
to get to know each other.
可以互相了解。
Mmm. Me, too. What a wonderful coincidence.
嗯。我也是。这个巧合真是太美好了。
There's no such thing as coincidence.
可从没有什么巧合。
That's what Schlomit always says.
那是Schlomit经常说得。
Oh, is this your family?
噢，这是你的家人吗？
Yeah. That's all of us at Aspen.
是的。那是我们全家在阿斯彭。
Aspen：位于美国中西部的科罗拉多州，以滑雪场而著称，是富人聚集区和度假胜地。
There's Schlo and, uh,
这是Schlo和，呃，
my son, Benyamin, and Sarah.
我的儿子，Benyamin，还有Sarah。
They're very sweet.
他们可真好。
No! No!
不！不！
Help!
救命！
Hank!
Hank！
No! Not my face! Not my face!
不！别咬脸！别咬脸！
Help!
救命！
I didn't wanna do that.
我并不想那么做的。
Fuck with me, you're gonna get hit by a book.
惹了我，你就会被本书揍。
That's what's gonna happen.
这就是要发生的事。
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
你特么一定是在逗我。
You know, it's funny.
你知道的，这很有趣。
When the family's away you find yourself thinking about things
当家人离开的时候，你会发现你自己在想一些
that you don't think about all the time.
一直以来你不会想的事情。
I bet.
我确信。
You think about who you were,
你在想你曾经是谁，
and who you've become.
而又会成为谁。
Mmm.
嗯。
Would you like to do some cocaine?
你想吸点可卡因嘛？
I'm sorry?
什么？
I'm just doin' some blow while the family's away.
我只是在家人都走的时候吸一点。
Would you like a bump?
你要来试试吗？
No, I don't think that's really, um...
不，我不认为，这实在是，呃……
I see.
我明白了。
I mean, not that I have a problem with...
我不是说我不赞同……
I mean, I do have a...
我的意思是，我确实……
Is this some sort... It's a test?
这是不是一个……这是个测试？
Oh, okay, I see what's happening here.
噢，好吧，我明白这里发生了什么。
You're thinking about all that talk about Piper Brothers values.
你一直在想那些关于派普兄弟价值的谈话。
But if you think situationally,
但是如果你分情况考虑，
friendship is a Piper Brothers value.
友谊也是一种派普兄弟的价值。
One of the big ones.
重要的之一。
And that's all that's happening here.
而这就是这里所发生的一切。
We're just hanging around, getting to know one other,
我们只是在闲聊，想了解彼此，
and doin' some rails.
然后想找点乐子。
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
But if that's not your thing...
当如果这不是你的喜好……
Well, uh...
嗯，呃……
Okay. Right.
Better make sure that Jay's not lost.
最好确认一下Jay没有迷路。
No, no, no! He's fine. Let's do cocaine!
不，不，不！他很好！我们来吸点可卡因吧。
Super!
好极了。
Oh, shit!
哦，糟糕！
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Wow!
哇！
See? That's what I'm saying. We get older and we forget.
看？这就是我要说的。我们正在变老而我们忘记了
People, they stop doing the things that they love.
人们不再做他们喜欢的事情了
And for some people, it could be surfing.
可能对某些人来说是冲浪
For some people, it could be traveling.
对某些人来说是旅行
For me, it's gettin' high
对我来说就是嗑药
and listen' to freakin' Slayer.
然后听非主流的Slayer。
Slayer：美国著名速度金属乐队，金属四巨头之一。
That just, like, blows my mind
这就会让我兴奋。
that that's what it is for you.
那，那就是它带给你的。
But that's your point. That's my point.
－但那是你的观点。 －这是我的。
'Cause it's so small-minded of me
因为这对我来说太小家子气了
to assume anything. Right?
－来假设任何事情。 －是吗？
Because I don't know you. You don't know me.
－因为我不了解你。 －你不了解我。
I don't know you. Yeah. You know the idea of me.
－我不了解你，是的。 －你知道我的想法。
The CEO that controls your future.
一个控制你未来的CEO。
But that's not me. No.
－但那不是我。 －不。
And it's like you, I'm sure there are things about you that nobody knows.
而就像你，我确定你有一些事情没有人知道。
Fuck yeah, there are.
太特么对了，确实有。
Can I show you something? Yeah!
－我能给你看些东西吗？ －当然！
Whoa.
哇哦。
Piper Brothers, 75 years.
派普兄弟，75年。
But very few people know about that.
但很少有人知道这些。
Whoa!
哇哦！
And there's more.
还有更多。
Eazy-E!
Eazy－E！
Eazy－E：被认为是匪帮说唱（Gangsta Rap） 史上最重要的人物之一，于1995年3月26日因艾滋病去世。
I miss him every day.
我每天都缅怀他。
That's so touching. Did you know him?
这真是太感人了。你认识他吗？
Annie, it's like... It's just... Lotta parts up in me.
Annie，这就像……这就是……我的一部分。
Wake up!
醒醒！
Wake up, you fuckin' cocksucker!
醒醒！你特么的混蛋！
Sm, how do you perform CPR on a dog?
Siri，怎么给狗做心肺复苏术？
CPR：心肺复苏术。
I found four places named "Starbucks."
我找到四个叫做“星巴克”的地点。
What the fuck is happening?
特么到底发生了什么？
And then you become a mother, right?
然后你就成了一个母亲，对吗？
And it becomes about the kids.
后来就是有关于孩子。
Which is great, because you want it to be about the kids.
哪个好，因为你想给孩子最好的。
But then you need time for yourself.
但是接下来你需要有自己的时间。
That's why I started writing.
这就是为什么我开始写作。
But it's, like, writing about Jay and the kids,
但它，就像， 写有关Jay和孩子的事情。
and then it becomes a job.
然后它就变成了一份工作。
But I love my job. I love my job.
但我爱我的工作，我爱我的工作！
But I need to work out. I need to work out.
但我需要发泄，我需要发泄！
It's not even for me.
这不仅仅是为了我。
It's, like, for everybody else.
这，好像是，为了其他人。
Because l'll go bat-shit crazy. Like, crazy, crazy, crazy.
因为我特么会发疯，就像，疯狂，疯狂，疯狂。
I ran track. I ran track in college.
我跑步，我在大学里就跑步。
But, you know, it's just so hard
但是，你知道的，实在是太难
to find the time. I know.
－找出时间。 －我知道。
To do anything, right? It is.
－不管做什么事情，对吗？ －没错。
If you don't do that, then you just sort of lose yourself.
如果你不这么做，那么你就有种迷失自己的感觉。
Do you want another line?
你还想再吸一点吗？
No, I'm still enjoying the first line quite a bit, thanks.
不，我还沉浸在刚才那些，谢了。
You are so easy to talk to.
和你聊天真是太轻松了。
I feel like you get me.
我觉得你很懂我。
Oh, God, I feel like we get each other. Yeah.
噢，上帝，我觉得我们都懂彼此，没错！
Where's your husband?
你丈夫在哪里？
I don't know! Where is that fucker?
我不知道那个混蛋在哪里？
What was that? Was that the doorbell?
那是什么？是门铃吗？
There's a lot of action here tonight.
今晚这里很多活动。
Yeah, there is.
没错，有很多。
Hey! Okay.
嘿！好吧。
Can I help you?
需要帮助吗？
Hi! I'm the mayor, Robby Thompson.
嗨！我是市长，Robby Thompson。
Pleasure to meet you. What's happening?
－很高兴见到你。 －发生了什么？
The mayor? Oh, not of this area.
－市长？ －噢，不是这个地区的。
I'm mayor of a different area.
我是另外一个地方的市长。
Of Thousand Oaks.
千橡市。
Of Thousand Oaks：美国的一个城市，位于加利福尼亚州。
He is the Mayor of Thousand Oaks
他是千橡市的市长，
and I am his First Lady of Thousand Oaks.
而我是他千橡市的第一夫人。
- Okay. - That's right.
－好吧。 －没错。
And we are out, just talkin' to people,
我们出来，就是和人们聊聊天，
um, spreadin' the word about Thousand Oaks.
呃，宣传一下有关千橡市的词。
What word?
什么词？
Uh... uh... Whew...
呃……呃……
Great town.
大都市。
It's a wonderful city to raise a family.
那是一个建立家庭的美好城市。
They have the winningest, uh,
他们有在全国总是胜利的，呃，
Little League baseball record in the country.
少年棒球联合会的记录。
Little League：美国少年棒球联合会，由8至12岁的选手参加。
Nobody gives a shit about Thousand Oaks.
没有人在乎什么狗屁千橡市。
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
我很抱歉，阁下。
"Your Honor." Please. "Your Honor's" my dad's name.
“阁下”拜托，“阁下”是我父亲的名字。
"Mr. Mayor" will be just fine.
“市长先生”就可以了。
Hello.
你好。
No!
不！
Sit!
坐下！
Fetch!
接着！
Anyway, we're out talkin' to people
不管怎样，我们是来和人们聊聊的
about Thousand Oaks
有关千橡市。
and we're collecting donations
而且我们正在筹款
for the Big Brother charity program.
为了“大兄弟”慈善项目。
Charity program. Of Thousand Oaks.
千橡市的慈善项目。
Of Thousand Oaks.
千橡市。
What is it with this new trend
这个逐渐倾向于做深夜慈善的新社会化
of late-night charitable solicitations?
到底怎么了？
I don't know. I have no idea.
我不知道，我也是一头雾水。
Uh, we definitely
呃，我们肯定
accept money. Eh...
接受金钱。呃……
But what we really need
但是我们真正需要的
are used iPads.
是用过的ipad。
That's a really good idea.
那真是个好主意。
It's a great idea.
这是个很棒的主意。
It is? I mean, really inspired.
－是吗？ －我是说，很有想法。
Yeah. I'm sure they could really use that.
没错，我保证他们能利用起来。
Well, I have one.
嗯，我有一个。
Oh! No.
哦！
Yeah. I have one right here.
对。它就在这里。
You actually gave me this.
事实上是你给我的，
I haven't had a chance to look at it yet.
我还没有机会看一眼呢。
Oh, I don't need it. Just give it to 'em.
噢，我不需要它，你还是给他们吧。
Do you mind if I just give...
你介意吗，如果我给……
God, no. Give it to 'em. I don't care.
上帝，不，给他们吧，我不在意。
It seems like a good cause.
这听上去是个很好的理由。
Thank you. Thank you. This worked out great.
－谢谢。 －谢谢。这会很有帮助。
Nice to meet you! Have a good night!
－很高兴遇见你！ －享受这个美好的夜晚！
Good night! Remember Thousand Oaks!
－晚安！ －记得千橡市！
Hi, I'm the mayor. iPad!
－嗨，我是市长。 －ipad!
There he is!
他在这儿！
Ariel! Hakuna matata!
<i>Ariel! Hakuna matata!</i>
Go play.
去玩吧。
Jay. What the hell happened to you?
Jay。你到底发生了什么？
I had an epileptic fit.
我癫痫发作了
In your bathroom.
在你的洗手间。
But your dog saved me.
但是你的狗救了我。
Because, in addition to diarrhea,
因为，除了腹泻之外，
I'm also an epileptic.
我也有癫痫。
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
噢，老天。你没事吧？
We gotta go. It is time for us to leave.
我们要走了，是时候离开了。
This is when we should get the hell out.
现在我们特么的应该离开了。
Now. Just now is when we should leave.
现在，就是现在我们该走了。
'Cause, you know, this is... Yeah.
因为，你懂的，这……对。
I did a little cocaine. What?
我吸了点可卡因，怎么了？
What?
什么？
Just one line. Just one line.
－就一条。 －就一条。
One what? A bump.
－一什么？ －一点儿。
What? She did a line. So?
什么?—她就爽了一下，怎么了 ?
Honey, let's just... Okay.
亲爱的, 我们先别...—好吧
Thank you so much for your hospitality.
十分感谢你的热情招待
You've been so amazing.
你真是太棒了
This is your cocaine straw.
这是你的吸可卡因的吸管
No, no, no. Please. Keep it.
不用了—你留着吧
Thank you.
谢谢你
Okey-dokey.
好了勒，两位
Thank you so much for helping
十分感谢你帮助
with our charity,
我们的慈善事业
but Annie and I need to get movin' on those kidneys.
但是Annie和我得继续为肾奔走了
Oh, I completely forgot.
啊，我完全忘记了
I need to go get my checkbook.
我得把我的支票本拿来
Thank you so much.
真是太感谢你了
What?
干嘛?
"Just one line"?
"只是爽了一下"?
Who are you? What was I supposed to do?
这还是你吗? —那我该怎么做？
Cocaine? That's the answer to that question?
那就磕药? 这就是你对刚才问题的回答吗?
He offered and I didn't wanna seem judgmental.
是他提议的，而我不想显得高高在上地评判他
It was peer pressure.
这是同辈压力
I was distracting him.
我是在转移他的注意力
With cocaine? What is this? Fuckin' Scarface?
用可卡因?这算什么?他妈的《疤面煞星》？
Are you giving me shit?
你这是在说我的不是了?
Is that what's happening right now? Yeah!
所以现在你就是在指责我？—没错！
Mm-mm. No, I don't think so. Annie.
恩.我可不管了—Annie
Annie. How is it that I get mauled by an attack dog,
Annie，我可是被一条恶狗咬伤了
I barely escape with my life,
拼了老命才逃了出来
you're in the living room doing blow with your boss,
而你在客厅和你老板嗨翻天了
and somehow, you're mad at me?
并且不知怎么地，你还对我发火？
What did I do? Oh, What did you do?
我干什么了?—哦，你干了什么？
You didn't erase the fucking video, Jay!
你没有删除那该死的视频，Jay!
I told you, Annie. I forgot.
我告诉过你了,Annie.我忘记了
"I forgot." "I forgot." I've heard you say that. "I forgot!"
"我忘了" "我忘了" 我听到你说的了 "我忘了!"
Okay, fine! I didn't forget!
够了！我没忘记删！
I made a conscious decision to keep the tape.
我做了个清醒的决定打算留着这个录像
And I was gonna keep it forever!
并且我打算一直留着它！
Because I had on video
因为我拥有的这个录像
what was one of the greatest nights of my life.
记录着我人生最棒的夜晚之一
And so I wanted to keep it.
所以我想要留着它
For myself.
为了我自己
And for my own personal reference use.
和个人参考使用
Yeah, you wanted it.
没错，你想要留着它
But I specifically didn't want you to keep it
但是我明确表示了我不想要你留着它
because I didn't want it to get out and guess what?
因为我不想它流传出去，猜猜看？
It did! It did immediately.
它马上就流传出去了!
That part was a mistake.
这部分是个错误
I wanted to save it for myself
我想为了自己留下它
and then the fuckin' app...
然后就是那个该死的应用...
Stop talking about the app,
别说那个应用了
'cause this is just typical of you.
因为这事就你能干的出
You do whatever the hell you wanna do all the time,
你他妈的就是随时随地干一切你想干的事,
and I do everything. I do everything.
而我就是跟在你屁股后面替你收拾
I hold this shit down, is what I do.
我干的就是把这该死的一切处理好
Clearly, you should not do cocaine.
很明显，你不该嗑药
Maybe I should do more cocaine.
也许我该多磕点
Because I've never done it before and I kinda like it.
因为我以前从没磕过并且我已经有点喜欢上了
I'm fairly certain the answer
我十分确定问题的答案
is not for you to do more cocaine.
不该是你磕更多的药
This sex tape. This night.
这个性爱录像—这个晚上
This is the kind of thing
就是那种
that reveals a lot about a person.
会揭示人很多问题的事情
Oh, really?
搞毛啊?
Reveals a whole lot about a person.
完全揭露了一个人
You know what? Just shut up.
你知道吗?还是闭嘴吧
I tried not to say it!
我没说话呢!
This kind of thing, a crisis,
这件事情,这个危机
reveals who someone really is deep down.
从本质上揭示了一个人
And you, you can't think about anyone else but you.
而你, 你根本不会为别人考虑
Okay, that is... Jay does what Jay wants to do.
等等，那是—Jay做一切Jay想做的事情
You have to go to a concert
你接连三个晚上
three nights in a row.
去一个音乐会
For work?
为了工作?
But that's my job, Annie. We're a team.
那是我的工作啊,Annie,我们是个团队
And part of what I do on that team is I work.
而我在团队里该干的就是工作啊
That's what makes me a good teammate, isn't it?
这就使我成为了一个好队友,不是吗？
I don't just wanna be a teammate!
我不想仅仅是做个队友
Why did we stop having sex?
为什么我们不再做爱了？
What?
什么?
Annie, it's not like we just stopped.
Annie, 问题不是我们不再做爱了
No, you know what I mean.
不，你知道我的意思
It's just, like, why did...
这就像是，为什么...
When did we stop needing to be close?
什么时候开始我们之间有了距离?
When did I become so annoying?
什么时候开始我变得这么讨人厌?
I don't know!
谁知道啊!
I think the coke is wearing off.
我觉得这可卡因的劲头有点退了
That's a bummer, man. I was having a blast. Really?
真是倒了血霉了.但拍的时候我还是很享受的—是吗?
We really gotta find out who's been sending
我们一定要搞清楚是谁
these fucking texts.
发了那些该死的短信
Are they...
他们是在...
They're having sex in our car.
他们正在我们的车里做爱
It appears that way.
看起来是这样的
Sorry, guys. Yeah, sorry.
不好意思了，伙计们—是啊，不好意思
I'm not even gonna ask if you guys...
我都不打算问你们是不是...
Yes, we watched the video.
没错，我们看了那个视频
You said you weren't gonna say anything.
你保证了不会说出来的
I know we weren't gonna say anything, but I can't lie to Jay.
我知道我们不能说出来,可我不能对Jay说谎啊
And besides, we just
而且，我们也只是
skimmed it because we didn't have time.
随便看了看，因为时间不够
Oh, my God!
我的天啊!
Annie, there is nothing to be ashamed of.
Annie, 这没什么好羞愧的
He's right. There's not.
他说的没错，不需要羞愧
At first, yes, I thought there was.
刚开始,是的，我也觉得那很丢人,
But now, I've seen it. And there's not.
但是现在,我已经看过了.这并不值得羞愧啊
No, it's the most natural thing in the world.
是啊，这是世界上最自然而然的事情了
I think this might be...
我觉得这该是...
No, it definitely is
不，绝对是
the most embarrassing moment of my life.
我人生中最尴尬的时刻了
Oh, no, no, no. You should not feel embarrassed.
哦，不不不，你不必要感到羞愧
If anything, you should feel proud.
如果有什么的话,你该感到骄傲
Yeah, your body's insane.
但是视频里，你身体感觉有点僵硬啊
Oh, my God. Okay.
天哪—好吧
Truly, I admire you for it.
说真的,我简直崇拜你
I can't believe that you let him watch it!
我简直不敢相信你让他看了!
I'm sorry.
对不起
He wanted to watch it. I wanted to watch it. Just a little peek.
他想看.我也想看.我们就偷偷看一眼
But then, we got very involved with it.
但是后来,我们开始投入进来了
We got really wrapped up in it.
我们可真是性致盎然啊.
Oh, my God!
要死了!
Oh, great dick, by the way.
哦，对了，胯下有神器啊
Yeah. Thank you.
呃.谢谢
Honestly, the whole thing was a big turn-on.
说真的, 这整个录像简直是强力春药啊
Oh, my God. We noticed. Yes.
天啊，别说了— 我们知道
Guys, could I have the iPad back, please?
伙计们，能把iPad还给我吗?
Really? I mean we... Dude!
什么？我想说...—大哥！
Okay, fine!
好吧!好吧！
There you go. You're obsessed with that thing.
给你.你可真是过分紧张了
Wait.
等等
We shall never speak of this night again.
我们要绝口不提这个夜晚
Absolutely.
当然了
Of course.
肯定的
I need a bathroom and an aspirin.
我要洗个澡和吃点阿司匹林
Yeah, yeah. Oh, of course.
当然了
Come on in. Please.
请进吧
Dad. Mom. Hey, pal.
爸爸.妈妈—嗨，小家伙
Hey, sweetie. Hi, Marta.
嗨.亲爱的—嗨.Marta
Howard is study. I was. In my room.
Howard在学习—我当然在我房间里学习
Annie, Jay.
Annie, Jay
What a surprise, you guys.
你们来可真是惊喜啊
We were just out, uh...
我们刚出去是为了...
gettin' a drink.
喝一杯
Celebrate the ol' anniversary.
庆祝结婚纪念日
Here. I'll get you an aspirin.
等会，我给你找阿司匹林
Okay. I'm gonna use the bathroom.
好的.我用一下卫生间
Want a shirt?
想换件衬衫吗?
Yeah. That'd be great. Thanks, bud. I'll get you a shirt.
当然.那太好了.谢谢了,老兄—我给你找件衬衫
Get outta my way!
别挡我路!
So, here we are.
好了,就我们两个人了
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是啊
Did you receive my text message?
你收到我短信了吗?
What?
什么?
Yeah. You know, you really should be more careful, Jay.
没错，你得要更加小心点才是啊,Jay.
Wait, are you...
等等,你不会就是...
No. 'Cause you're just too...
不可能. 你还太...
Is this a...
这是...
Stop babbling already, Jay.
别再废话了, Jay.
I think we both know that I already own your ass.
我想我们都明白你已经逃不出我手心了.
You own my ass?
我逃不出你手心了?
What, do I have to spell it out for you?
什么,我非得要和你把话说开吗?
I have your sex tape.
我有你的性爱录像
You're fucked.
你完蛋了
I got news for you. What?
我得告诉你一件事—什么事？
I got the iPad back.
我要回iPad了
You got the iPad back? Yeah.
你要回iPad了?—是的
That's fantastic, man. Good effort. Look at me.
那太棒了.兄弟.努力没白费啊.看着我
Do I look like a kid who knows how to make
我看着像不像一个
a simple copy of an MP4 or do I not?
知道怎么做份简单的MP4拷贝的孩子？
Yeah, you do. And look at you.
你看着像—再看看你这衰样
Runnin' around trying to collect up
东奔西走,趁着还有时间拼命收集
all your iPads before time runs out.
你所有送出去的iPads
Why didn't you just remote wipe them?
你为什么不远程清除那些录像?
You can do that?
你能办到?
Fuck!
我操!
Fuck me!
I almost murdered a dog.
我差点谋杀了一条狗.
Yeah.
呵
But I already uploaded your sorry-ass video
但是我已经上传了你那可怜的视频
to a site called YouPorn.
YouPorn：黄片网站名
到一个网站.叫做YouPorn
Should be up by tomorrow morning.
明天一早估计就能顶到首页了
And sadly, the only one that can take the video down
遗憾的是,唯一一个能把视频撤下来的人
is the original poster and that's me.
是视频的原始发布者,也就是我
Okay, this is a...
好，这该是...
I got it. This is a joke, right?
我明白了.这是个玩笑,对不对？
You're joking.
你在开玩笑
You didn't put...
你并没有把视频放到网上...
What do you want? Hmm.
你要什么?—恩
You want an Xbox?
你想要台Xbox?
You can get me an Xbox? Do you want an Xbox?
你能给我一台Xbox?—你想要台Xbox？
Like, the new Xbox? Yeah.
就是新的Xbox?—是的
What do I look like to you, Jay?
我看起来像你吗, Jay?
A fucking idiot? No!
一个白痴? 不!
I want $25,000 in cash.
我要2.5万现金
$25,000?
2.5万?
Howard. First of all, I don't have $25,000 just sittin' around.
Howard.首先,我现在手头上没有2.5万
And besides, what are you gonna do with $25,000?
话说回来,你要拿2.5万干什么?
I'm gonna buy a horse.
我要买匹马
Yeah, I'm gonna buy a motherfucking horse
没错, 我要买匹该死的马
to keep my bitches happy-
让我的姑娘们开心
I think it's time for me to have a little talk with your parents.
我觉得是时候得和你的父母谈谈了
Try. Go ahead.
试试吧.尽管去
I'll lie.
反正我会撒谎
They're gonna believe me. Not you.
他们也会是相信我,而不是你
Oh...
对了...
And don't you dare tell Annie about this.
如果你敢把这个告诉Annie
I'm gonna tell Annie.
我会告诉Annie的
Okay-
好吧
But before you do, just think about
但是在你告诉她之前，给我想想
these three words for me, all right?
这三个词，好吗?
School. Email. Blast.
学校. 邮件.身败名裂.
Man! I need some ice cream. Who's in?
我的天! 我得来点冰淇淋.谁想要?
Deal with it, Jay.
坦白面对吧, Jay
You're fucked!
你死定了!
I got just so much pressure inside me.
我真是承受了太大的压力
Good talk, pal. Seriously.
交流愉快,伙计.说真的
Honey.
亲爱的
Let's go home and keep calling
我们回家吧，然后一直打
that number until someone answers.
那个号码直到有人接听
I just wanna know who's sending these texts.
我就是想知道到底是谁发的那些短信
Uh-Oh.
<i>啊噢</i>
Uh-oh. Wanna do the thing?
啊噢. 想不想来点尝尝?
Wanna do the four-flavor thing?
想不想尝尝四种口味的?
Yeah, let's do that thing. Yeah.
当然.我们来好好尝尝
Robby, there's no easy way for me to say this,
Robby,没有轻松的方式告诉你这个事实
but your kid is trying to blackmail me
你的孩子正在试图勒索我
for $25,000!
要价2.5万!
Jay, can you hear yourself right now?
Jay, 你知道自己现在在说什么吗?
I mean, look. You've had a stressful day, right?
我是说,听着.你今天一天承受了这么大的压力, 不是吗?
Howard's just a kid. He's not your problem.
<i>Howard只是个孩子.他不会是你的麻烦的</i>
When you wake up, you'll realize that.
当你一觉睡醒,你就能明白了
Would you just go check his computer, huh?
你为什么不去查查一下他的电脑, 啊?
Check his phone!
<i>查查他手机!</i>
For me? Jay.
为了我?-Jay
I'm not gonna look at his computer.
我是不会去查他的电脑的
Because there's nothing on there.
<i>因为那儿不会有什么的</i>
He told me and I trust him.
他告诉过我了并且我信任他
This is Howard we're talking about.
我们谈论的是Howard啊
I gotta go. Okay.
<i>我</i>得挂了<i>好的</i>
Get some rest, all right? I'll see you at school tomorrow.
好好休息，好吗？明早学校见
Oh, shit. Right, graduation.
我擦.对了,毕业典礼
I forgot. Oh, and, hey.
我忘记了—哦，对了
I just wanted to say one more time, man. Great tape.
我就是想再说一遍，兄弟，那真是个好录像啊
I mean, I had no idea that Annie was so flexible.
<i>我是说，我一直不知道Annie居然这么灵活</i>
Robby. Robby. Yeah?
Robby. Robby.—怎么了？
Maybe we should just stop talking about this now.
也许现在真的不适合谈论这个
Yeah, yeah! Fair enough.
对对!说的在理
Another time. Yeah. Or, you know, never.
下次吧—或者，永远都不
Another time.
下一次吧
Mom, thank you so much
妈, 真是太谢谢你了
for coming by on such short notice.
这么匆忙通知你赶过来
Oh, of course, honey. Of course.
没关系，亲爱的
Oh. Thank you.
谢谢
Annie. ls everything all right?
Annie.一切都还好吗?
Yeah, yeah. It's fine.
是的，都挺好的
And you and Jay? You're okay?
你和Jay之间都好吗?你没事吧？
Yeah, I think so.
是的，一切都好
You sure you don't wanna tell me what's goin' on?
你确定不打算告诉我发生了什么?
Yes, I'm sure.
是的.我确定
Maybe some other time.
也许以后告诉我
Never
绝不
There's some things that I really wanna share with you,
有些事情我很想告诉你
and then, there's some things.
但是，也有些事情
That you should die just never knowing
你情愿死都不想知道
Okay, sounds good. Okay.
好吧，听起来可以，我不问了
What are you doing? Jesus Christ!
你在干什么呢？—我滴个神啊！
Hi. You can't keep doing that to me.
嗨.你不能再这么吓我了
What are you doing, Jay?
你到底在干什么, Jay?
I have really good news.
我有个好消息
Great news.
非常好的消息
I remote wiped the mailman's iPad.
我远程清除了邮递员的iPad
I erased his iPad from my computer.
我从我电脑上删掉了他iPad上的视频
You can do that? Yes, you can.
你会?—是的，我会
We did it.
我们做到了
So, yeah.
所以，没错
In a way it would've been nice to have that information earlier.
从某种角度上来说，早些知道了这个消息再好不过了
In another, more important way,
而从另一方面，更重要的一方面
it's great news that we have
远程清除了邮递员iPad上的视频
remote wiped the mailman's iPad.
真是个好消息
Yeah, it's good news.
是啊，真是个好消息
What's the bad news?
那坏消息是什么?
What?
什么?
$25,000?
2.5万?
Where we gonna get... We don't have $25,000!
我们从哪儿搞...我们根本拿不出2.5万!
We're not giving it to Howard! We're not. It's insane.
我们才不会把钱给Howard!—我们不可能会,这简直疯了
We're gonna let this little freak show
我们就打算把这个可怕的视频
just post it up on the Internet
发布到网上
for the entire world to see?
让全世界看见?
People that we know? People we don't know?
给我们认识或者不认识的人看到？
God, my gynecologist is gonna be so
天啊，我的妇科医生
Okay. Disappointed in me.
一定会对我非常失望的—好吧
The deli guy's gonna see what we did with the salami!
那个熟食店的家伙会看到我们用意大利香肠干了什么!
Babe, can I say something that's gonna
亲爱的, 我能说些
sound kinda crazy, but just go with me?
可能听起来有些疯狂的话，但是让我说下去?
All right? I've been watching a bunch of
好吗? 我已经在网上看了
these videos online,
一大堆这种视频
and you cannot really tell
你真是大多认不出来
who these people are. Mostly.
这些人到底是谁
And I'm sure that they all have
并且我也能肯定他们都有
somebody that they don't want seeing their videos,
不想被看到的人
but they make them anyway.
但是他们还是被看光了
Like this one video I saw,
就像这个我看过的视频
"Corn-fed Cowgirl Gets Milked."
"质朴女牛仔牛奶湿身"
There is no way that she wanted her boss seeing that
她不会想要她老板看到的
because what happened there seemed very personal.
因为这发生的一切看起来是十分私人的
Your point is? My point is,
你的重点是?—我的重点是
if our video went up there, God forbid,
如果我们的录像在网站上大受欢迎,但愿不会如此
does anybody even know that it's us?
真的会有人知道那是我们俩吗?
And if they did,
并且如果有人知道了那是我们俩
does it really matter that much?
那真的要紧吗?
I mean, it might.
我的意思是.可能会
The coke-bender Hank Rosenbaum might not care.
那个瘾君子Hank Rosenbaum也许不会在意.
But the CEO of Piper Brothers Hank Rosenbaum,
但是作为派普兄弟公司CEO的Hank Rosenbaum
he might.
他就会在意
Honey.
亲爱的
Hank Rosenbaum has an 11-inch
Hank Rosenbaum的床头柜里有一个11英寸
double-sided dildo in his nightstand.
双面的假阴茎
Is it made by Piper Brothers?
那是派普兄弟公司制造的吗?
Look, my point is,
听着,我的重点是
maybe everybody has an 11-inch dildo in their nightstand.
也许每个人的床头柜里都有个11英寸的假阴茎
That's a beautiful metaphor, honey. Thank you.
这真是个绝妙的比喻,亲爱的—谢谢
I thought of it just then.
我刚想到的
Maybe we don't care so much
也许我们不需要在意
about what other people think.
别人的看法
I have an idea.
我有个主意
What? We haven't even seen this video yet.
是什么?—我们到现在为止还没看过这个录像呢
There's no chance I'm watchin' it.
我是不可能去看的
You don't have to. I'll watch it.
你不用看，我来看
And at least, then, we'll know
至少，看过之后，我们会明白
what we're actually dealing with.
我们到底是在处理着什么？
Here we go.
要开始了
We gotta get this thing off the fucking Internet!
我们得把这个录像从该死的网络上撤下来!
Why? What?
为什么? 怎么了?
I saw it! That's us.
我看见了! 那就是我们啊
That's definitely us. Very clearly.
那绝对就是我们.太明显了
That camera's fuckin' amazing. Oh, my God!
摄像头太他妈高清了—我的天啊
Remember that thing I told you about porn?
还记得我告诉过你的关于黄片的事?
About how you see right past the guy?
关于对片子里男的的看法?
Well, I saw him and it's me
是的，我看见他了，而且那是我
and it's fucking horrible!
这实在是他妈的恐怖了!
It's like the worst picture of yourself ever.
这就像是你最丑的相片
Except you're fucking for hours.
除了你还被人看着做爱做了几个小时
What about me?
那我呢?
You? You're a fucking sexpot
你? 你就是个他妈的天生尤物
I've told you this. Total wank material.
我告诉过你.这简直是手淫的好素材
And now you're gonna be in the fucking cloud!
并且你将会那该死的云终端!
Oh, my God. We have to do something.
哦，天哪—我们得干点什么
We need 25 grand to pay off Howard.
我们得付给Howard2.5万
Hell no! Fuck Howard! I have another idea.
才不要!去他的Howard!我另有个主意
Okay. You said it was on YouPorn, right?
YouPorn：黄片网站名
好的.你说过录像是在YouPorn上, 对吗?
We're gonna be on it. Jesus Christ.
我们将会在这网站上.上帝保佑
I know, honey. We're not. Relax, okay?
我知道,亲爱的.我们现在不是还没有吗.放轻松，好吗？
The Internet is not a free-floating thing.
互联网可不是个不受约束的东西
It's on a server somewhere.
总归还是有个服务器的
It's not like it's an actual cloud.
这不像真的在云端，我们遥不可及
You knew that, right?
你知道的,对不对?
Yeah.
对
Look, we find a business address.
看,我们找到了一个商业地址
It's probably in the Valley somewhere.
它可能在山谷区的某个地方
Most porn companies are.
大多数黄片公司也在那儿
We're like 20 minutes from the porn capital of the world.
我们离世界黄片之都大概只有20分钟的车程
Well, then what do we do?
那好,接下来我们该干什么?
I don't know. I mean,
我不知道.我是指
it's probably just a few guys with computers.
那地方可能就几个男的和电脑
这个公司里大概也就几个人几台电脑
We'll beg 'em
我们去求他们
or bribe 'em or something.
或者贿赂他们或者做点其他的什么
That's a great idea.
这真是个好主意
What do we do with the kids?
那孩子怎么办？
We can't call my mom again.
我们不能再让老妈帮忙了
Up here, make a right.
直走，右拐
I think this is it.
应该就是这儿了
Hello? Open up!
有人吗？开门啊
Hello! Is anyone there?
你好，有人吗？
This is the last time I'm gonna ask. Is anyone home?
我再问一遍，有人吗？
Hey! Hey, bud!
嘿，嘿小盆友
Hey! How's it goin', man?
嘿，大盆友咱们在做什么啊？
We're just having a little adventure.
我们只是在进行一场小小的冒险
What's the adventure?
什么样的冒险？
It's kind of, like, what? Like, a scavenger hunt.
就像……你知道的，类似派对上的寻宝活动
You know what it is? It's a game.
你知道是什么吗？一个冒险游戏
Uh-huh. And it is called,
嗯嗯……他的名字是
Breaking and Entering. What?
-破坏且闯入 -神马？
Okay, great.
哦，好吧
Shh.
嘘……
Hello?
你好？
有人吗？
What are we looking for?
我们在找什么啊？
That's a good question.
这是个好问题
Yeah, we're not exactly sure.
我们不确定到底在找什么
"Central Data Core."
“中央虚拟存储”
- This is it. - Let's do it.
-就是这个 -让我们开始吧
I think I might've underestimated
我想我大概错误的估计了
the size of YouPorn.
YouPorn的工作场所尺寸
Yeah, it's a bit bigger
是的，这个比你刚刚想的
than you would think.
要大一些
Jay! My God, what have we done?
Jay! 我的天，我们做了什么
We're gonna go to jail, Jay!
我们会去蹲监狱的，Jay
We should get outta here. Yeah. We should go!
我们应该离开，是的，离开这儿
May I help you?
我能为你做点什么？
Okay. You guys stay here. Okay?
你们这些小家伙留到这儿好吗？
Okay-
好哒
May I ask what the fuck is goin' on here?
我能特么的请问一下你们在这儿干嘛呢？
May I ask if you're the proprietor
请问你们是这个机构的
of this institution?
拥有者吗？
"Institution?"
“机构”？
Yeah. I'm that motherfucker.
是的我就是那特么的拥有者
And you've just made a very serious mistake.
以及你们刚刚翻了一个巨大的错误
Where are you from, huh? You from Hustler?
以下出现的都是各种奇怪的色【囧】情网站的名字_(:зゝ∠)_
你们是哪儿派的间谍，Hustler的?
Um... Huh?
嗯。。啊？
No.
不是的？
Which crew you runnin' with? Xtube?
以下两个名字皆仿照油管YOUTUBE
X管派的你们？
Is that it? No? RedTube?
是这个么？不是？红管？
Bangbros? No.
-干干兄弟帮？-不
BangBus? No.
-干干车?-不是
BigBoobAlert?
小心大胸袭来?
You with BigBoobAlert? Nope.
-你们是“小心大胸袭来”的人？-不是
Where you from, then? You tell me right now.
你们到底是哪儿来的？告诉我
Wait, no, don't tell me.
等等，让我自己再猜猜
- MassageCreep? - No.
-指尖AV?- 不
We're not from MassageCreep. No, no.
我们不是“指尖AV”派来的
KungPaoPussy?
约炮之家？
No. No.
不是的
You from BeaverBong? Tugjobs?
你们是海狸帮的？强制做活儿的？
TrannySurprise? Nutflix?
Tranny的惊喜?蛋蛋flix?（仿Netflix
- No, ma'am. - RealityKings?
-不是的女士。-现实之王？
NaughtyAmerica? Euro-Angels? AsianAngels?
美国小淘气?欧洲小天使? 亚洲天使?
SeducedByACougar? FuckStarTV?
熟女诱惑?与星共滚?
Huh? Those cunts? Not us.
-嗯？那些“妹妹”?-不是我们.
SubmitYourBitch? No, sir.
上传你家小婊砸？-不是的
Wankspider? No.
-手淫蜘蛛？-不是
MonkeyCum?
小猴射射?
Honey, what's that one that Larry runs? AThousandCumShots?
-甜心，Larry开的那家叫什么？-天涯共此潮？
MonstersOfCock? No.
-怪物丁丁？-不是的
You with LadyBonersHD?
你们和高清蠢蛋女士？
ButtholeSandwich.com?
三明洞？
Sir, we are in no way affiliated with ButtholeSandwich.
先生，我们不是三明洞的人
You one of them assholes
那你是“奶油胸派”派的
from BigTittyCreamPie.com?
傻蛋吗？
- No. - No.
-不是 -不是
Not Playboy.
不是花花公子派来的
Did Hugh send you?
是“休”派你们来的吗
Listen, sir. If you could just give me one minute to explain.
先生，你可以给我一分钟让我解释下吗？
I know... See, this is the thing.
我知道，看，这是事情结果
You've put me in a position
你置我于此
where my only options are to beat your ass,
只能打你们一顿或者
or call the goddamn cops.
叫那些混蛋警察的境地
Okay, sir, I see where you're coming from...
好的，先生，我看出了你们……
Actually, I think we should beat their ass and call the goddamn cops.
实际上我们可以先打他们一顿再叫警察
I was thinkin' the same shit.
我现在也是这么想的
Look, if you want to kick my ass, fine.
揍我一顿，好吧
And if you want to call the cops, so be it.
你们还想叫警察，叫吧
But there is a reason that we did this, and it's because
但是我们这么做是有原因的，因为
sometimes people do some really crazy shit to protect their families.
有时人们总会头脑发热的做一些事情
And that's what happened.
这就是一切的原因
We did some crazy shit.
我们拍了些很糟糕的东西
We're really sorry.
我们十分抱歉
We're really sorry. We're honestly...
我们十分抱歉，非常……
It was for our family.
这并不是为我们家所做的
You motherfuckers.
你们这群傻蛋
You made a sex tape
你录了一部性爱录像带
and now you're tryin' to get it off my server.
你现在想把它搞出我的服务器
Daddy, can I pet the doggies?
老爸，我可以喂喂这些小狗吗？
No, we can't pet these doggies.
不，不行的哦
What are your freakin' names?
你们叫了什么奇怪的名字？
I'm Jay. Annie.
-我是Jay -Annie
Annie and Jay? Yes, ma'am.
-Annie和Jay?-是的女士
You the Annie that writes
Annie你是那个作者吗
"Who's Yo Mommy?"
"Who's Yo Mommy?"的
Yeah.
嗯
- I love your blog. - You do?
-我喜欢你写的博客 -真的吗？
I read it all the time. Oh, that's so great.
我一直在读那些，炒鸡棒的
I mean, the way you write about
我想说，你写的这些……
motherhood and parenting.
当妈的生活啊怎么做父母什么的
Your marriage.
你的婚姻
Oh, thank you. How old are yours?
哦谢啦，你的孩子多大？
Oh, one's 18 months and one's 52 months.
哦一个18个月一个52个月（一岁半和四岁四个月）
Aw.
哦
Baby, it's Annie and Jay.
亲爱的这是Annie和Jay.
Yeah, well, I'm afraid Annie and Jay
是的我知道Annie和Jay恐怕
are in deep motherfuckin' shit. Shh.
惹上大麻烦了-嘘
Baby.
北鼻
All you had to do was email me
你们要做的只是给我发电邮
and I would've taken it down.
我就会撤下视频的
Do you have any idea how many people
你知道有多少人
are makin' sex tapes out there?
录了录像带吗？
We get about 1,000 new ones every day.
每天有1000支新的啊
I don't need to be puttin' up sex tapes
我不需要更新那些
from people who don't want their sex tapes up there.
不想上传他们录像带的人们的录像带
There's no shortage of sex tapes.
性爱录像带是不会短缺的你们造吗
Okay? You didn't have to break my fuckin' door!
好么？你特么的根本不需要搞坏我的门！
We're just incredibly sorry, sir,
我们太太太太对不起您了，先生
and we will pay for all the damages.
我们会赔您这些损失的
Oh, yes, you will. Today.
是的，你们会的，今天就会
And you will be incredibly grateful
你们会感到无比的感激
that I feel sorry for your asses
为你们感到“抱歉”
and that my wife likes your blog.
我老婆喜欢你的博客
No, we are very, very grateful.
是的，我们无比感激
Super grateful. Thank you.
超级感激谢谢你
It is great of you.
您真的太好了
Internet porn gets a bad rap in some circles,
互联网上的av在某些圈子里名声不好
but it's not deserved.
但它们并不是如此
I'm always tellin' people this. YouPorn is a community.
我经常告诉别人Youporn实则是个社区
A safe, supportive place where people can go
一个人们能来的安全舒适的地方
to display videos of themselves ass-fucking each other.
来展示它们互相滚床单等等的地方
That's really nice.
这是十分棒的
It's wonderful.
很精彩的网站
I think so.
我也是这样认为的
But let me ask you something.
让我问你们一个问题
Why'd you make the video in the first place
你们为什么一开始录了这只录像带，
if you didn't want anyone to see it?
却不想让别人看到
I mean, I know why you did it.
我想说我知道你这样做
But what about you?
但你为什么也参与进来了？
It was my idea, actually.
实际上这最初是我的想法
I just guess it was something different, you know.
我想着这会使某些事变得不同
Something new.
去尝试一些新鲜的事
Yeah, that's what I thought. "Something new."
哦，我知道了你想表达的如何的“新鲜的事"
Let me tell you somethin'. I've see a lot of fuckin' sex tapes.
让我告诉你们一些事，我看过很多盘性爱录像带
It's not something people do
这经常不是在一切感情顺利的时候
when everything's goin' great.
人们开始做这种录像
It's what you do when you've lost track
这是你们忘记了你们的初衷时
of why you're fuckin' in the first place.
弥补它所以录的
It's a quick fix.
一个快速的重新修复
But it doesn't solve anything.
但这并不能拯救任何事
And a lot of times it just hides bigger problems.
这样的次数多了就会隐藏更大的问题
Look at Paris Hilton and Ricky Salomon.
以下的人名均为美国名人，都已分手
你们看看Paris Hilton和Ricky Salomon.
Pamela Anderson and Tommy Lee.
Pamela Anderson和Tommy Lee.
Pamela Anderson and Bret Michaels.
Pamela Anderson和Bret Michaels.
Vince Neil and Janine Lindemulder.
Vince Neil和Janine Lindemulder.
Janine Lindemulder and me.
Janine Lindemulder和我
All of these relationships had bigger problems.
这些感情下面都有着巨大的问题
They all forgot why they were fuckin'
他们都忘了第一次
in the first place.
他们滚床单的原因
Anyway,
不管怎么说
that'll be roughly $15,000. How would you like to pay?
大约要赔我15000美金，你们怎么看？
I think that went pretty well.
我觉着进展还不错
I know. He was so nice.
-我知道-他人不错
Oh, my God. What time is it?
哦我的天，现在几点了？
We have to be at school for graduation at 9:00.
我们必须在九点前赶到学校参加毕业典礼
We have to get ready, you guys.
我们要准备好哦
I gotta gel my hair.
我需要弄好我的发型
Come on! Come on, come on, come on!
快点快点快点快点
♪ I don't wanna be so complicated
<i>? 我并不想如此复杂</i>
Go, go, go! We got this!
快快快~我们可以的
♪ Down in a new river
<i>?顺着新的河流而下</i>
Okay, babes. Eat up, eat up, eat up.
好的,宝贝们快吃快吃
Through the thing and magically, barn!
通过这里，神奇的事发生啦，好啦
Let's see it.
让我们瞧瞧
Pretty good.
不错哟
Hairbrush!
梳子
♪ A simple new life ♪
<i>? 简单的新生活 ?</i>
Okay, let's go.
好了，走吧
But I gotta get this on.
我必须要穿上这件衣服
Put it on in the car. Go, go!
在车里再穿吧，快走
Whoa!
哇哦
I gotta go backstage.
我要先去后台了
Go. Go graduate, pal.
伙计快跑
- We love ya. - Bye.
-爱你哦-拜了个拜.
Mommy, I'm gonna go find my class, okay?
妈咪，我要去找我班里的小伙伴去啦
Okay, honey.
好的，宝贝
All right. We'll catch ya after. See ya. Bye!
好吧，等会接你哦
Hey, there we go.
到那儿吧
Okay. Oh, great. Perfect.
-哦好的 -没错
Sorry.
抱歉
We made it. Yeah.
-我们做到了-是啊
We got 'em all back.
我们收回了所有的备份
I mean, we may have to steal Howard's computer later.
我知道，我们等会要偷howard的电脑
But how hard can that be?
但这有多难呢
Hi.
嗨.
I don't think I'm ever gonna be able
我不认为我还能再直视robby
to look at Robby the same way again.
和原来一样了
I'm pretty sure the feeling is mutual,
我觉着这件事情是相互的
if that helps at all.
如果这样能让你感觉好点的话
I love you.
我爱你
I love you, too.
我也爱你
No. I mean it.
不我是认真的
Like, not in the way
不像是普通的那种
that we say it to each other all the time.
每天都在讲的我爱你
I mean, I really love you.
我想说，我真的很爱很爱你
And I'm also really sorry about the video,
对于录像那件事我也很抱歉
if I hadn't said that already.
如果我之前没有这样说的话
Thank you.
谢谢啦
You hadn't.
不用
In a way, though, I'm also
同时我对于这件事情发生了
really glad that it happened.
也感到挺开心的
'Cause I was thinkin' about
因为我也在想
what you said at Hank's.
你在Hank家所讲的那些
You said that a thing like this,
你说有一件事就像
like "the video incident,"
“录像”事件一样
reveals a lot about a person.
揭示了很多东西
And you're right.
你是对的
And you know what it revealed about you?
你知道揭示了你的什么吗？
You are generous.
你的慷慨.
You're kind.
你的善良.
You're imaginative.
你的想象力很丰富.
You always remember what's important.
你总是记住什么是第一位的
You're ready for anything.
你对任何事情都做好了准备
You're a bit of a lightweight when it comes to cocaine.
你嗑药以后有点轻飘飘的
But I think that is a great quality.
但我认为这是一个好品质
I just think that you're really amazing.
我刚刚就在想你真的太棒了
That's why I'm fuckin' you in the first place.
这就是我们为什么会开始滚床单的原因
Oh...
哦……
You know what this revealed about you?
你知道你的潜质是什么吗？
It revealed that you would do anything
你愿意做任何事情
to get those iPads back for me.
去把那些有着录像的iPad拿回来
And there is no one I would rather be with
没有一个人比你更让我愿意
when the shit hits the fan.
在惹祸上身时陪伴着
God, I lucked out.
老天，我太走运了
I lucked out.
是我太走运了
I fucking love you.
我真特么的喜欢你
Excuse me. Public place.
抱歉，请注意下
Oh, hi, Mom. Excuse me. Hi.
-哦，嗨，老妈. -让一下
Good morning, everyone.
<i>Good morning, everyone.</i>
Let's all settle in and find a seat.
<i>让我们找到座位坐下.</i>
My name is Principal Rodriguez and I would like
<i>我是PrincipalRodriguez以及我真心</i>
to welcome everyone
欢迎你们所有人
to our fourth-grade graduation ceremony.
<i>在我们四年级的毕业典礼上.</i>
First up, I'd like to introduce
<i>首先，请让我介绍</i>
our video yearbook maestro,
<i>我们的年间视频制作者,</i>
Clive Hargrove. Yeah!
<i>Clive Hargrove.耶~~</i>
Whoo!
哇哦~~~
This is a video I made
<i>这是一个有关</i>
showing the amazing year we had.
<i>我们超级精彩的今年的视频.</i>
Taking pictures and videos is really important
<i>挑选照片和视频是十分重要的</i>
Because it reminds us
<i>因为他包含了我们</i>
what's really important
<i这就是他重要的原因</i>
Aw...
and all the amazing times we had.
<i>我们一起度过的美好时光</i>
So now I present to you our fourth-grade video yearbook.
<i>所以现在请让我展示咱们四年级的年鉴视频</i>
You erased the video off of our computer, right?
你把电脑里的视频删除了，对吗？
Right, Jay?
对吗, Jay?
Is it Video 1 or Movie 1?
是 电影1 还是 视频1 呀
Video 1, I think.
视频1，我认为
I love you. Call 911. Okay.
我爱你，帮我叫911
It's Video 1. No, wait, it's Movie 1.
是 视频1, 不对, 是 电影1
No! It's not Movie 1.
不，不是 电影1 .
Wait, is it the most recent one?
等下，是最近的那个吗
Yeah, No! the most recent one.
是，不，最近的那个
What's Frankensync? Hurry, honey, hurry.
什么是Frankensync?快点，亲爱的，快点
It's okay. it was the right thing to do. He's fine.
没错的，他在做正确的事情.他好着呢
Shit. Are you okay?
卧槽，你还好吗
I'm not okay, man.
哥们，我不好
Okay. Uh, uh...
好吧，啊……呃……
Why doesn't Tess bring you to the hospital
Tess你为什不带他去医院呢
and I'll just make sure your computer's okay.
我看着你的电脑
Dude! That's insane.
-伙计-这很疯狂
You take him to the hospital.
你带他去医院
I will make sure the computer's okay.
我看着电脑
No, wait, I feel like I'm being...
不，等等，我觉着我被
Careful, careful, careful.
小心，小心，小心
- Hey, guys. - Hmm?
- 嘿，伙计们
Let's just take a minute and acknowledge
让我们花一分钟去确认
that we have a lot to celebrate.
我们有很多值得庆祝的事儿
Your mom gettin' an offer on her blog.
你们的老妈的博客得到了资金
I'll get it. So why did you jump off the balcony?
我知道了，但你为什么从台子上跳下啊
I told you, sweetie. I tripped.
我告诉过了亲爱的，我被绊倒了
That's why it's very important
所以那些栏杆的设置是
to always use the railings,
很有必要的
and to label your videos properly.
以及要正确的标注你的电影
Can I go get some ice cream with Howard and Marta?
我可以和Howard和Marta一起去吃冰激凌吗
Um...
嗯
No. Why not?
-不行 -为什么呀
Because it's family night.
因为这是家庭之夜
And after this I think we should all go get some donuts.
看完电视后我觉着咱们可以一起去吃甜甜圈
And maybe laser tag.
或者去打激光枪战
- Awesome. - Are you sure?
-酷~-你确定？
You can barely move over there.
你差不多不能移动诶
She's right.
她是对的
I'm sure.
我确定
Howard. Jay.
-Howard.-Jay.
We told you, Clive is busy tonight.
我们告诉你了，Clive 今晚很忙
A moment, please.
就占用你一会儿时间，求你了
So? I see what you're up to, asshole.
所以呢？混蛋我知道的你目的
I have no idea what you're talkin' about, Howard.
Howard我不知道你在讲什么
Withholding Clive.
控制Clive.
Looks like I might have some moves of my own.
看起来我应该采取一些方式了
Might wanna watch your back.
你也许要小心点哦
Are you threatening me, Jay?
你在威胁我吗，Jay?
I ain't payin' you shit, motherfucker.
我才不会给你那多钱的，小混蛋
Have you seen what I'm capable of?
你见识过我的能耐了吗？
I jumped off a fuckin' balcony.
我从看台上跳了下去
You do not want to cross me.
别想跨过我的底线
I don't care anymore. And that makes me fuckin' dangerous.
我在也不介意了，我会很危险的
Yeah, boy.
是的，男孩儿
This is the last copy
这是最后一份
of your stupid tape. All right?
你那冒傻气的录像带的拷贝，好吧？
I deleted all of the other copies.
我删了所有其他的拷贝了
Why should I believe you?
我凭什么相信你？
Doin' it for Clive.
对Clive的做的一切
To protect him.
保护他
Can't have this shit out there,
我不能在拿着它了
so I'm makin' a sacrifice.
所以我做了牺牲
Plus, he's kinda my only friend
再加一句，他貌似是我唯一的朋友
and I really wanna hang out with him.
而且我非常想和他一起出去玩儿
I can respect that decision.
我可以接受这个决定
Believe me, Jay.
相信我, Jay.
This is harder to give back to you
给你这个是件难事儿
than you could ever imagine.
你根本想象不到
Yeah. It's a good move, though.
是的，但是这是不错的一步
Let go of the fuckin' thing.
松手啊
I'll be by tomorrow.
我明天再来
I'll see ya then, you fuckin' weirdo.
明天见，怪胎
That's it? Yep.
-就是这个了？-是的
That's the last copy.
这是最后一份拷贝
Okay?
你确定？
Hmm?
嗯?
Wait!
等等？
Just this once? Just this once.
-就看一次？ -就看一次
And we don't even have to watch the whole thing.
而且不用看完全部
We can just skip around a little bit. Okay? Mm-hmm.
就跳着看一点，好么？
Hello.
<i>你萌好~~.</i>
Hi.
<i>你们好~.</i>
And welcome...
<i>欢迎。。。.</i>
I'm glad that we didn't go fucking roller skating.
<i>我对于咱们没去滑冰太特么开心了</i>
Put your leg between my butt cheeks.
把你的腿放到我屁股两侧
And then you lick my armpit.
然后舔我的腋下
Really? Mm-hmm. That's what it says.
-你确定？-他就这样写的
All right.
好吧
Armpit it is.
舔腋下啦
How is it?
这怎么样？
It's fine.
感觉还好
I'm gonna be so impressed.
我印象会很深刻的
Okay, here I go.
好哒，我来啦
One, two, three.
一，二，三。
Okay. Good?
好吧，就这样？
All right. Get in there. Should I come in?
来吧，到这儿，我确定到这儿么
Oh, wow. Yeah.
哦,哇哦，耶
Okay? Yeah.
这样？耶
- Yeah, totally, come on. - Yeah? Okay.
-是的，完全要这样，-这样？好的
Yeah. Of course, honey.
是的，就这样，哈尼
Oh, my God. This is so cute.
哦我的天，这好可爱
Thank you for doing this. This is my dream.
谢谢你这样做，这是我的梦想
Always wanted to do this.
总想这样做
- You got such a great outfit, honey. - Thanks.
-亲爱的你服装超棒！-谢谢
♪ Take me out to the ball game
<i>? 带我去那场球赛</i>
♪ Take me out to the park
<i>? 带我去公园呆呆</i>
♪ Buy me some peanuts and Cracker Jacks
<i>?花生和饼干请给我买</i>
♪ I don't care if I ever get back
<i>?我不在乎你是否回来</i>
♪ One, a-two, a-three strikes you're out
<i>?一 二 三振出局离开</i>
♪ At the old ball game ♪
<i>? 在那场古老的球赛 ?</i>
You ready?
你确定?
Yeah. Totally.
是的，完全确定
On!
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊！！！
My balls! My balls!
我的蛋蛋！！！！
No, don't touch me, don't touch me! Please!
哦，别挨着我，别挨我
Do it!
来吧！
Ow! Fuck!
哦！我屮艸芔茻！
Oh, my God! I kneed you in the vagina!
哦我的天！我磕到了你的“妹妹”
Honey, I ran track in college! I can do this!
亲爱的，我在大学是田径队的，我一定能做到！
On! Oh...! Oh...!
哦~哦！哦！
You stuck the landing!
<i>你成功降落了!</i>
♪ Oh, they don't know what love is...
<i>?哦他们不知道什么爱才是……</i>
Yee-haw! Wow!
耶~~哇哦~~
♪ They don't know what love is...
<i>? 他们不知道爱情如何.</i>
♪ But l-l-l-l-l-l...
<i>? 但我、我、我</i>
♪ I know what love is
<i>♪ 我知道爱情是什么</i>
♪ Come on, baby
♪ Let's show, show them how to do it
♪ Do it
♪ Do it, do it, do it, baby ♪
♪ Oh, oh...
♪ Yesterday just another day
♪ Just like any other day
♪ For we going to change this mind
♪ Keep around like we've got mountains of time
♪ Won't you come and sit down?
♪ Yes, right here on the ground
♪ Tell me the story of how we met
♪ Not that I never let you forget
♪ I wanna be yours I wanna be ours
♪ I wanna do the stuff in the back of your car
♪ I wanna be good I wanna be cruel
♪ I wanna be the girl that you wanted in high school
♪ I wanna be a model I wanna be clever
♪ I wanna feel this way forever
♪ I wanna be the one I wanna be the one
♪ I wanna be the one that makes you come undone
♪ Oh...
♪ Oh, oh...
♪ You can make me feel like a girl
♪ Just shout out the rest of the world
♪ Lay your head on my heart
♪ Or you can just pull my body apart
♪ Yesterday, just another day
♪ Just like any other day
♪ I think we just changed this mind
♪ We've got tiles of times
♪ I wanna be yours I wanna be ours
♪ I wanna do the stuff in the back of your car
♪ I wanna be good I wanna be cruel
♪ I wanna be the girl that you wanted in high school
♪ I wanna be a model I wanna be clever
♪ I wanna feel this way forever
♪ I wanna be the one I wanna be the one
♪ I wanna be the one that makes you come undone
♪ Oh, oh...
♪ I wanna be yours I wanna be ours
♪ I wanna do the stuff in the back of your car
♪ I wanna be good I wanna be cruel
♪ I wanna be the girl that you wanted in high school
♪ I wanna be a model I wanna be clever
♪ I wanna feel this way forever
♪ I wanna be the one I wanna be the one
♪ I wanna be the one that makes you come undone
♪ Oh, oh...
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
♪ You look so much better now that you have found her
♪ So much better with your arms around her
♪ In a world that's all your own
♪ Never spend another night alone
♪ You look so much better
♪ You look so much better...
♪ You look so much better now that you have found her
♪ So much better with your arms around her
♪ In a world that's all your own
♪ Never spend another night...
♪ Alone... ♪